Jay.
Jay. What? What's wrong?
You're snoring.
Me?
Oh, I'm sorry. I-
Hey.
Look at her.
Come on. We said
no Stella in the bed.
Oh, but she's just
a little puppy.
She probably got scared
and snuck in.
Oh, really? How come when
Manny has nightmares,
you don't let him
snuck in the bed?
Gloria, it's 6:00 in the morning.
Can we talk about this later?
Answer the question, Jay.
You know, I'm going to check the lease,
but I'm pretty sure...
we're not allowed to have
a meth lab.
You are a delight.
So what are you doing? I think
you're gonna like this.
I'm going on a juice fast.
Mmm.
Love it.
Hate it.
Let's face it. A well-fed Cam is
hardly a model of emotional stability.
Now, deprive him of food,
and stage by stage, it's
a slow descent into madness.
Stage one- the clean sweep.
Poison. Poison. Poison.
Do you think this is the best
week to be doing this? Why not?
Well, we have that charity thing
at my boss's house.
So what? I'm supposed to
put off my quest for wellness...
until we're no longer
socially in demand?
That will never happen.
I'm too charismatic.
No. No, not the cookies!
Of course the cookies.
Why do you always
want me to fail?
Stage two- attack Mitchell,
because when his diet
crashes and burns...
into a giant pile of Nutella,
I'm the one
he's going to blame.
Well, no, not this time.
You know what?
I'm gonna do the fast with you.
I think it's a great idea.
And we should do it together,
so we're on the same team.
You know, us versus food.
I know what you're doing.
And I really appreciate it.
Oh, no. It'll-
it'll be good for me.
I've actually
put on a few pounds, so-
Yeah, well- I didn't
want to say anything.
As the stock market plummeted,
brave young men
took to the skies,
ushering in
the golden age of the daredevil.
How awesome are people?
So awesome.
You want
to get that, buddy? I'll pause it
Hey, Luke.
How's it goin'?
Hey, Uncle Mitchell. I really can't talk.
I'm tryin' to watch a movie.
Oh, okay. Well, I just wanted to
drop off this bag of junk food.
Go on.
Uh, Cam and I
are on a juice fast,
so having the stuff
in the house just-
I connected the dots.
See ya.
Uh-
Seeing that weird, wonderful little man
pursuing his dream of walking on a tightrope...
made me think maybe I
could pursue my dream.
There you go, buddy.
Of walking on a tightrope.
# Hey, hey #
# Hey ##
Come on, Dad! You got this!
You can do this!
Stay focused,
stay hungry!
You okay, buddy?
What? Yeah!
Yeah, no, just proud of my dad!
There was a lot of chocolate
in that bag.
Phil- Honey, you gotta
take Luke to school.
Got it.
Okay, I haven't fallen three
out of the last four times.
This afternoon, we go airborne.
Yeah.
Yeah!
Yeah! Mmm!
Sitting all by
yourself at the table.
Now, where have I
seen that again?
Oh, right. Every day in
the school cafeteria.
I do that by choice.
School's choice.
Isn't that your nickname? Haley!
Be nice to your sister.
Alex- Good save.
Mom, sign this.
What is it?
They finally bumped me up
to the harder math class.
Third period, Mr. Waters.
What? No, Mom. You cannot sign this.
This is my class.
You're a freshman. What are you
doing in second-year math?
You're a senior. What are you
still doing in second-year math?
Not still. Again.
Alex, be nice to your sister.
Haley, not a good save.
I knew it would suck
having you at my school.
Well, hang in there.
A couple more years,
you'll have it all
to yourself again.
Come on, girls.
Jay, look at this.
It's ruined!
Stella did this.
She chew on my shoe.
You have to discipline
that stupid dog.
I discipline her all the time.
Oh, really? How?
By buying her little cupcakes?
They're not real cupcakes. They're
doggie treats in the form of cupcakes.
Yeah. You should've told that
to Manny before he ate one.
Ah, come on. His coat never looked better.
You wouldn't find this so funny
if she was destroying your shoes.
Well, I don't leave my shoes
laying around, so-
So it's my fault that
she chooses to chew my shoe?
I didn't say that.
You barely said it.
- You have to stop coddling her.
- I don't coddle her.
What?
She tries to drink the water.
it's funny!
You don't look at me in class.
You don't text me.
Who would text
during a class?
What are you?
Honey, I realize that this situation
is not ideal for either one of you,
but sometimes we just
rise above things.
Yes?
Excuse me. Did you notice the
curb here is painted yellow?
Uh, no, I did not.
Wow. It means
"loading and unloading."
Okay. Well, I was just
dropping off my kids.
And yet, I see no kids
emerging from the vehicle.
Well, we were chatting.
Wow.
At the risk of surprising you a third time,
Officer, I've been dropping off here for years-
Move it.
Okay. You betcha.
What was her problem?
You know what you
should have said to her?
Nothing. I should have said nothing.
What would be the point?
I have to see her every day.
I mean, why make it worse?
That's exactly
what I'm talking about.
Awkward, unpleasant situation?
Rise above.
Have a nice day.
Yeah.
Love you.
Bye-bye.
"And yet I see no
children emerging from the vehicle."
How would you like to
see my fist emerging into your face?
Oh! Now I think of it!
Day four of the juice fast,
and I'm hungry,
but I'm feelin' pretty good.
Cam, on the other hand,
has gone all Girl, Interrupted
After one, throwing out all of
our food, and two, blaming me,
he entered stage three-
soap actress.
I just wish my sister
would put herself out there more.
She has so much to offer!
Why are men so superficial?
That was followed by stage
four- a rush of epiphanies.
I don't need food.
Look at this.
Architecture's everywhere.
Oh, Spaniards make
amazing athletes.
Into stage five- despair.
Daddy, we hided,
but you didn't seek.
Cam?
Then came rage.
Ow! Ah.
Hey.
Whatcha got there?
The good news is, Cam's never made
it this far into a diet before, so-
Downside? I have no idea what
the next stage is gonna be.
But I'm pretty sure
it's not charming party guest.
Cam, I-l was thinking, I'll take the
bullet tomorrow night at my boss's house.
You don't have to go
to the party.
Th-They're boring.
Some... silly cause.
You know,
lots of people.
Parking.
- Cam, say something.
- Why do you hate me?
- I don't hate you.
- Then why are you trying to push me out of your life?
Because you seem a little...
unhinged.
Okay. You know what I think?
You should worry
a little bit less about me...
and a little bit more about yourself and
what you're gonna wear tomorrow night,
because I saw
what you have laid out,
and I don't think you're gonna
like the way you look in photos.
I hadn't landed on that.
Her hand's in the air,
like, every five seconds,
and she actually reminded
Mr. Waters to assign homework.
The class loved that. Do you
know how embarrassed I was?
Not as embarrassed as I was when
she said eight was a prime number.
Eight, Mom.
Okay, fine.
You know what?
I'm gonna call the school today
and have your schedules changed.
But I want you to know, a little
part of me died today, okay?
I thought the two of you could understand how
being in the same class would benefit you both.
Alex, you-you could've
tutored Haley.
Haley, you could've helped Alex
with her social skills.
Come on. The two of you could've
been two super-Dunphys.
And instead, what are you?
Two bickering half-Dunphys, and
I'm the fool that expected more.
You know what-
How do you ever-
I don't even want to hear it.
Just go upstairs. Go.
Wow. What was that?
That was a master class
in parenting.
Right now, our daughters are upstairs,
making a decision they think is their own,
but really it was an idea that
was skillfully implanted by me.
Inception Claire.
Dangerous game, but I like it.
Mmm.
What are those?
Wire walkers.
You want to go to the dance,
you gotta wear the shoes.
Luke, grab your camera.
Luke!
I wasn't sleeping!
Honey, I-l think
those are jazz shoes.
Nope.
Tightrope shoes.
Got 'em at an estate sale.
Only worn once.
That is not
a ringing endorsement-
Oh!
Phil, honey- Please be...
careful, all right?
Watch the door.
Hey, what'd you get
for number three?
You're not going to learn
if I just give you answers.
Well, what if I gave you
something in return?
Like what?
You can talk to me
in class.
I want lunch at the cool table.
- Then I want all the answers.
- Then I want a week at the table.
- That'll cost you two pop quizzes.
- A month.
- The midterm.
- Deal.
Lookin' great, Dad.
With these steps,
I break the surly bonds-
Chicken in a basket!
Don't look at me.
Mom? Mom!
What? What, what, what?
Mom, did you
call the school yet?
Uh, not yet,
but I was just about to.
Ah, Bartles and Jaymes!
Good. Because we were thinking we
might want to stay in that class.
Really? Oh, girls,
I don't know about that.
- Oh, please let us try it.
- Super-Dunphy.
I can't hold her.
I can't hold her!
Well, maybe one more week.
Thanks, Mom.
I don't know.
A cup of soup, a Cobb salad.
Yeah, it had bacon.
Hey, Cam, I don't have all day
to describe all my meals to you.
Stop eating all
my things, you stupid animal.
No, Cam, not you.
I'll call you back!
Bad doggie!
You want to chew on something?
Okay, okay, okay.
Look at this. Look at
this delicious man shoe.
Eat it. Come on.
Eat it. Eat it!
Mmm. Yummy.
Eat the shoe!
Eat his shoe.
Come on. Eat his shoe.
Yum, yum, Wm, Wm-
Yeah. Like this, look.
Delicious!
Mom?
Drop it.
- I w-
- Please. I'm sorry you had to see this.
Hello.
Hi, Mrs. Dunphy. This is
Rose from the principal's office.
Could you hold for Principal Weller?
Yes.
No, no, no, no.
Hi, Claire.
Hi, John.
What'd she do this time?
Actually,
I've go! both of them in here.
Both of them?
Really?
Alex was letting Haley
copy her home Work.
Mr. Waters caught them.
I-l don't believe it.
I'm about to have a little talk with them,
so the they'll be out a few minutes late.
Uh, I'm so sorry, John.
And honestly, I-I really am a
better mother than this, I promise.
So you've said.
Mm-hmm.
Seriously?
Seriously? Oh!
Excuse me.
Hey, um, what the hell is this?
This zone is for loading and unloading,
not for talking on the phone.
Yeah, I know, but
I was talking on the phone...
to the school that my kids
are about to come out of, so-
Are you aware this zone
has a time limit?
N-No, I'm not.
Wow.
You know what?
I do want to do some unloading.
I know your type.
Life has been bad to you.
It has made you feel small.
And then one day, somebody
gives you a fake cop outfit,
a toy badge
and a little SpongeBob tie.
Suddenly it's payback time,
right?
Well, I got news for you, Law and
Special Parking Unit.
It's not my fault.
I'm really sorry, Dad. Oh, it's all right.
Everybody throws up at school.
If I had a nickel for every time I puked at
school, you know how much money I'd have?
Thirty-five cents?
Exactly. Now, go get cleaned
up, and I'll call the doctor.
Wait, Dad. I don't need a doctor.
What's up?
The other day, Uncle Mitchell
brought over a bag of junk food...
so he and Cam could do
a Jew fast.
Juice fast?
I'm pretty sure
he said Jew.
But anyway, I took the bag,
and I hid it, and I ate it all.
Oh, buddy.
I couldn't help myself.
I'm weak.
Don't look at me.
It's all right.
it's okay.
Hey, you learned a lesson. A painful lesson.
I guess we both have.
What do you mean?
I always saw myself as a guy who could
soar through the sky, dancing on a wire.
I can't even get across one
six inches off the ground.
Well,
maybe that's the problem.
Maybe you keep falling because part
of you knows that you can fall.
Maybe if the wire was much,
much higher, you wouldn't fall.
Oh, Luke, Luke, Luke.
You are a genius.
Come on. We got work to do!
Yes! Can I have a doughnut first?
Yes, you can!
Ah, there they are.
My Super-Dunphys.
We're sorry, but we just-
Ah, ah, ah.
You don't get to talk!
You had a chance
to be better people today.
You, to be more well-rounded,
and you, to be a better student.
You could have elevated the Dunphy name,
but instead you chose to tarnish it.
So congratulations, ladies.
You brought this family
to a new low.
Mom, are you-
Yeah.
Yeah, I am.
And I would actually like to get
these loosened up, if I might.
Are we gonna have
any more trouble?
No, ma'am.
Claire, do you
need me to drive the girls?
All good, Janet.
Real good.
Goat cheese
risotto ball?
No, thank you.
Are you sure?
They're so good.
Walk away.
It's tough enough to deal with
Cam when I'm at full strength.
But I have been fasting
just as long as he has,
and I do not have
the energy...
to deal with
a big, needy brisket case-
Bras- Basket case.
Cam! Don't be mad at me, but I think
that you really need to eat something.
What? You're supposed to
be my support.
Oh, away from me, temptress.
And I never thought I would
call you that in a negative way.
I've seen her do
a lot of crazy stuff,
but this
is a whole new level.
- Is this a people cookie?
- You're good.
A definitive yes or no
would be appreciated.
Those cupcakes
did a number on me.
Are you happy?
You have reduced me
to a person who eats a shoe.
Gloria, sit.
Do you think this is funny,
to talk to me like I am a dog?
I'm not talking to you
like you're a dog.
I'm just asking you to sit, so we
can get to the bottom of this.
Okay, fine.
Good girl.
Come on. You set me up.
Gloria, why are you
acting so crazy?
It's just a little dog.
It's not the little dog
that is making me crazy.
It's you that
is making me crazy!
Me?
Yeah.
You used to put me first! You
used to want me in that shower!
Should I be here for this?
No, Manny, it's okay.
I go.
But I want you to know this. Where
I come from, man cherish woman.
It goes wife, mistress, dog.
Dog always at the bottom!
As you can imagine,
I get asked to help, uh,
with a lot of these
environmental causes.
Usually, I buy a ticket, bid on
Shaquille O'Neal's big shoe-
and, uh, come home.
But then, something happened.
Um, I love paddle surfing.
And each time I'd go out,
I'd see this one sea lion.
He'd pop his head up,
he'd check me out.
I got so used to seein' him,
I even named him- Snorkels.
God, I do not like where this is going.
So one day, I, uh, I go
out, and I see Snorkels.
But he's doin' this weird
twisting thing in the water.
- Oh, God. Oh, God, oh, God.
- Shh. Shh.
So I paddle over, and I see he's
got a plastic grocery bag...
wrapped around his neck
and one of his fins.
And I freaked. Tried to get
it off with my paddle.
Didn't work,
so I jumped in,
but he disappeared
under the water, and, uh-
Don't say it.
Don't you dare say it.
And I never saw him again.
Oh. This is the saddest
thing I've ever-
Mitchell, are you okay?
No, of course I'm not okay.
None of this is okay.
Okay. You need to pull yourself together,
'cause we're at your boss's house.
He drowned, Cam!
Okay.
- Is he all right?
- Yeah, yeah. I think he just needs a little air.
You know who else needed air?
Snorkels!
Excuse me.
Where are you, Snorkels?
Mitchell, get back here!
Oh, Snorkels.
Mitchell,
what is wrong with you?
What do you think is wrong with me?
I'm starving!
Well, if you're starving,
then just eat something!
I can't eat something, because
then you'll get mad at me,
and we're at
my boss's house.
I'm not gonna get mad at you!
I appreciate what you're doing for me.
I'm doing it for you.
Oh, you don't have to do anything for me.
I love you just the way you are.
I love you
just the way you are.
Whoa!
Okay.  I got you!
I got you!
Thank you.
I got you! I got you!
I got you! I can walk.
I can walk.
I think Mitchell may just be
a work friend.
I letdown
my mom and dad today-
Worse than that,
I let down my teacher.
It's all my fault. Everything
I touch turns to detention.
I'm sorry, Mom.
Me too.
I don't really have a whole lot
of moral high ground to stand on.
I wasn't exactly my
best self today either.
All in all, not a great
day for the Dunphys.
Come on, Dad!
Believe in yourself!
You're making the impossible unimpossible.
Phil. Oh, my God.
Don't even bother. He's in the zone.
He can't hear you.
Go, Dad!
You got this!
All Week long, I've been
telling my girls how to act...
instead of showing them.
But not Phil.
Phil could have said, "Alex, relax.
Don't take everything so seriously." ...
Or "Haley, challenge yourself
Don't give up so easily."
But instead of talking the talk,
Phil Walked the Walk.
And isn't that what we're supposed
to do for the people We love ?
It's definitely a challenge.
Right, two, three.
And left, two-
But Phil made it look easy
seven feet off the ground.
Oh!
- You're awesome!
- Oh, my goodness.
Turns out I've had
my Super Dunphy all along.
Yeah!
Ohh!
What was on my mind as I was
walking across that wire?
I kept thinking,
"If I can do this,
then I've got two ways
of getting across my yard."
Did you have fun?
Yes.
She's the cutest doggie
in the whole world.
Yeah, I heard you
the first time.
Let's go find
your daddies.
We're in here.
Oh, my God. These
cupcakes are so good.
I'm so sorry we helped ourselves.
We were so hungry.
They are delicious.
I love that they're not
too sweet, you know?
Mmm. They taste almost
like pété. I mean-
But why are you eating?
Well- Been on a juice cleanse.
You need to mind your own
business, sweetie, for now. Yeah.
Mmm.
English - US - PSDH