- Honey, what is all this?
- Hey.
Hey, Mom, I'm trying to write this
stupid college essay question,
- and I really don't even know where to start.
- What's the question? Tell me.
"What's the biggest obstacle
you've ever had to overcome?"
Didn't my third-grade teacher
say I had, like, A.D.D. or something?
Oh, no, honey.
She said you couldn't A-D-D,
and she put it that way because she
also knew you couldn't S-P-E-L-L.
Wait. Slow down.
Ohh!
Sweetheart, what's this? We
talked about this last week.
I said I'm building Luke a tree house.
You said "Fine."
You know, sometimes I think
you just tune me out.
I never told her.
She just would've said no.
I don't remember agreeing
to this, Phil.
This is like the time you
backed down the driveway ...
with a hang glider
sticking out of the car.
If you'd let me keep that, those geese
would've followed me to the wetlands.
You would have died.
A hero.
So we spread out a nice blanket,
open up a bottle of vino ...
and watch the sun set
over the water.
It was majestic.  Mmm.
Majestic.
Ay. Why we never
have the picnic?
Who wants to sit on a blanket? There's
no back support. it's majestic.
Last week, Shorty took me
to see the Cirque du Soleil.
It's like a circus, but classy.
So if you like elephants,
don't hold your breath.
She's so cute.
Jay hate the crowds,
the beach, the rainbows.
Rainbows.
That's just colors in the sky.
Do we have to pull over every time
and take a picture?  Shame.
There's an expression
in Italian, Jay:
Dammi la tua mano e corriamo
uniti per tutta la vita.
"Give me your hand and we will
run together our whole lives."
Aww. Jay
also hates running.
# Hey, hey #
# Hey ##
- Here you go.
- Oh, thank you.
- And here you go.
- Ohh. What is this?
You said to knock
your socks off.
Oh? Well, look. it's already working.
Two more of those, and you won't
be wearing any underwear either.
Oh, look!
Cam, down. Down.
Maybe later.
Oh, okay.
Maybe- Maybe later.
Did you hear that? The
waitress is flirting with me.
No, no. She's not
flirting with you.
She's trolling for tips, okay?
She totally knows you're gay.
How would she know I'm gay?
Uh, maybe it's the way you ordered
a "drink-a-doodle-doo."
Cam has this crazy theory that if he
were straight ...
And Julia Roberts were single,
they'd be dating.
It's not crazy. I met her once at an AIDS
walk, and our chemistry was palpable.
No, you handed her a bottle of water.
And her fingers lingered.
Because you wouldn't let go.
I could totally pick up
any woman in here.
If by that you mean lift her off the
ground, then yes, I'll give you that.
I for sure could be a womanizer.
Or you could be someone who just stepped
out a machine called The Womanizer.
Okay, you know what? That's it.
Pick anyone in here,
and if I can get their number,
you do the laundry for a month.
If I fail, I'll do it.
Okay, I hate doing
laundry, so, um- Mm-hmm.
No. Um-
Oh, okay.
Right here.
Her.
Okay, great. Great.
Just get rid of my flair.
Whoa. Where-
Where did Cam go?
Where is he?
- Dinner was absolutely wonderful.
- Amazing.
You know what? Why don't you guys come
salsa dancing with us tomorrow night?
Oh, yeah.
That would be great!
A y, it sounds like so much fun.
I love salsa dancing.
Jay, let's go
salsa dancing with them.
Look.
Why not? I just bought
that pay-per-view fight.
I'll tell you what.
We'll compromise.
We'll watch the fight,
we'll eat salsa.
- Who needs him? Come dancing with us.
- A y, no. I wouldn't want to-
No, no, you'd be
doing me a favor.
Shorty never wants to stop,
and I could use a break.
You hear that, Jay?
I never stop.
All I hear is
she could use a break.
Hey. Oh, my God.
How are you?
Hey. Hey!
Wow.
Look at you.
You look fantastic.
Thank you. S-So do you.
How long has it been?
F-Feels like forever.
Yeah.
What, um- When is the last
time we saw each other?
Oh, let's see. I think
it was at Dave's thing.
You know what?
I'm sorry.
I don't know
if you've heard.
I was in
a terrible car accident,
and ever since the coma,
I have a really hard time
placing names and faces.
So who are you again?
Oh, my God. I am so sorry.
It was just a clever way to try to approach you.
We don't know each other.
I've never been in a coma.
But you so deserved that.
That was
the worst pick-up ever.
Oh, my God!
That was genius
and mean!
Now I know why
we're old fake friends.
Can I buy you a drink?
Yeah.
I'm Katie.
Cameron.
If she were a hot guy, I would
never have been that smooth.
It's ironic.
Like the Gift of the Vagi.
There we go.
Thank you. Nice to meet you.
You too.
Bye.
Wham, bam,
thank you, Cam.
Seriously. You got her number?
Sure did.
And all my shirts get ironed, and their seams
should appear straight, just like their owner.
Shouldn't you be using
screws instead of nails?
America was built
with nails, Son.
So was that gazebo you built
for our Fourth of July party.
I'm telling you,
you are gonna love this bad boy.
You know
what can't climb trees?
Raccoons?
Worries.
Raccoons can and will get up
here, so don't leave any food,
or they'll get territorial
and attack.
Are you sure this is a good idea?
Are you kidding me?
You're gonna have so much fun hanging
out up here with your buddies.
Trust me. When you get
older, it all changes.
Why?
Well, life gets in the way.
Did I just say "wife gets in the way"?
'Cause sometimes I do that.
Nope, you're good.
And you have
lots of friends.
Yeah, I have work friends, and your
mom and I have couples friends,
and there are my college friends, but
they're scattered all over the country.
It's not the same as just shouting
out to your neighborhood buddies,
"Hey, fellas, I'm up here
in the tree house!"
Oh! I gotta fix
that ... board.
I can't do this. Why
are you so frustrated?
Because I've never had
any obstacles to overcome.
Oh, honey,
that's not true.
Really? Name one.
Well-
You're lactose
intolerant.
Oh. "Dear college, cheese makes me gassy.
See you in September."
Sweetie, you're not really starting
your essays "Dear college," are you?
What difference does it make? I've lived
a boring, sheltered, pathetic life.
I am sorry we have made things too
easy and comfortable for you.
Oh, you should be.
it is all your fault.
You have shielded me from everything
interesting and dangerous.
You are blaming me because I
kept you from getting hurt?
Gabby's mom's a hoarder.
That essay
practically writes itself.
Maybe it is our fault.
But did you ever consider
there's a reason?
What are you talking about?
There's a reason
why we were so easy on you.
- I don't understand.
- Oh, honey, you're old enough now.
- Old enough for what?
- The truth.
Okay, come on.
Gotta show you something.
- We're gonna go for a ride.
- Mom, just tell me.
You are my mom, right?
Oh, hey.
- I'm a bad man.
- Oh, no. What did you eat?
Mitchell, remember the girl
I met last night?
How can I forget her? She's super famous
for having the world's worst gaydar.
How could I be so cavalier
with her emotions?
You know, we had a real connection.
She gave me her number.
And right now, she's probably sitting
by the phone, waiting for me to call.
Uh-huh.
I don't think you understand
how charmed she was by me.
Oh, my God. Where did you
get all this self-confidence?
I won Cutest Baby
at the 1974 Jasper County Fair.
People at the time
said I could go Gerber.
You know what? I'm calling her.
What?
No, I can't carry this around.
I have to come clean so she
can move on with her life.
This is crazy. She
is not waiting by the-
Hi. Katie, it's Cam.
First ring.
- I was hoping I would call too.
- Oh, smooth.
So listen, I forgot
to mention something last night,
and I'm- I'm actually not really
quite sure how to say this.
"I'm a gay guy."
Um, it's actually
somewhat delicate.
"As am I,
on account of the gay."
No, no. I had a great
time with you too, Katie.
It's- Well, it's just that-
"I don't dig the ladies."
No, no, and I want you to sit. I want
you to have a seat on a chaise lounge.
Hey, you wanna go out and grab some
dinner before the fight tonight?
No, thank you.
Wanna eat at home?
I'll grill some steaks,
open a bottle of wine.
Whatever you want, because
I'm not going to be here.
She's going salsa dancing-
without me.
Ay, Manny, I told you.
it's a 21-and-over club.
A forbidden dance floor.
Only makes me want it more.
Wait a second. You're going
dancing with Shorty and Darlene?
Yes. Because even though he's old
like you, he still likes to have fun.
We like to have fun.
Last week, I took you to dinner.
Went to the boat show.
Got some sherbet.
And were home by 8:30
with no boat.
What do you want from me?
I don't like dancing.
I don't like sherbet.
Yeah, right.
How about coconut?
Who doesn't like the coconut?
Hmm? Who?
And anyways, I'm going
dancing with or without you.
Fine. I hope you have
a good time with Shorty.
I don't need Shorty.
I won't have any problem
finding a partner on my own.
Wow.
Way to rub it in, Mom.
How'd it go, heartbreaker?
That is one classy lady.
Which is why I couldn't tell her.
- What?
- Well, I just couldn't do it on the phone.
She seemed so excited
to hear from me,
and I'm very bad at
disappointing people, Mitchell.
Not all people.
Mama was right when she said my
charm was like a wild stallion.
If not properly bridled,
it'll bust down a barn.
Okay, you wanna get rid of your
girlfriend, tell her that story.
Maybe I will when she comes over.
She's coming over.
Are you serious?
She said she was in the
area, running errands.
What was I was supposed to say?
"Don't come over"?
Well, I guess I could've said
that, but it's too late now.
Plus, I wanna break it
to her gently.
So come on.
Help me un-gay the place.
You know what? I'll make it less gay by half.
Oh, these flowers should go too.
You mean the ones underneath the
portrait of you cuddling another man?
Oh, good catch.
Ohh!
Manny.
What's up, big guy?
How hard is it to learn this salsa
dancing stuff? Not hard at all.
It's about tapping into your emotion,
your passion and your inner fire.
Crap!
I stink at dancing.
First dance at our wedding, Gloria
was all graceful and gorgeous,
and I was all big and clunky, like
that scene from Beauty and the Beast
Actually, that was the song.
Manny picked it.
He didn't like me back then.
Salsa ]
Back straight.
Okay, do as I do.
Other leg.
Okay, stop marching. You're
dancing, not invading Poland.
Hello. Hi.
Looking for Jay Pritchett.
He's about 6'2", tough guy,
wrestles with homophobia.
The hell are you doing here?
I had to get
out of the house.
Cam needed a little alone time with
his new girlfriend. Don't ask.
Don't tell.
- What's going on here?
- He's learning to dance.
But he's just so tense.
It's not working out.
'Cause you're not letting go.
I'm trying.
Don't you think I wanna be all smooth
and make your mom happy out there?
But I just can't do it,
that's all.
Jay, I'm not giving up on you.
Okay. Hey, Manny, would
you give us a second?
Oh.
Thanks.
Dad, look.
L- I know this is weird,
but you and I are a lot alike.
You're self-conscious, okay?
So, um- Here. Just-
The hell is this?
It's just something that some people
take at clubs to, you know, loosen up.
You take this?
A gay man who hates dancing
lives in a sad and lonely little world.
This just melts your inhibitions,
and- and you can dance all night.
- Plus, it gives you a raging-
- I don't wanna-
I don't like this at all. Just
hold on to it, just in case.
Keep it. It's fine.
Jay, I'm gonna
show you something.
A farmer in New Zealand
taught a pig to dance.
Whoa.
See how he keeps
his snout up?
Oh, yeah. This is it.
This is what?
This.
I- I can't do this.
I can't get out of the car.
I'm sorry.
I'm too embarrassed.
Would you just tell me
what's going on? Okay.
I- I- I want you to go read
what's carved on that tree.
Mom, you're freaking me out.
Just do it.
Do it, Haley.
Have fun getting home!
There's your obstacle!
What?
Are you kidding me?
Oh! Son of a ... biscuit!
Why does that keep happening?
Maybe I need a nail gun.
Okay, that's it.
I'm out.
What do you mean, you're out?
Where are you going?
Dad, no offense, but I've
seen you with a glue gun.
I think a nail is gonna be
harder to get out of my hair.
No, don't go.
I'm doing this for you.
Are you, Dad? Are you?
The kid made me
think with that one.
Who was I really
doing this for?
Sometimes I just say,
"Are you, Dad? Are you?"
Because he gets real quiet and
doesn't notice when I walk away.
It's weird, because I feel so
comfortable around you already.
You know, last night,
when I got home,
I just started thinking ...
about all of the fun things
that we could do together.
You know?
Yeah.
I don't wanna scare you off, but my sister's
getting married in a couple of weeks,
and I so don't wanna go
to that thing alone.
Maybe you could be my date.
Katie, you're an amazing woman.
You're smart, you're beautiful,
and how fun is that handbag?
This is gonna come
as a little bit of a shock.
I'm fairly gay.
Don't know why I said that.
I'm- I'm totally gay.
Just gay.
You're telling me you're gay?
Yeah.
Why? I was born that way.
You know, it's just-
No, why are you telling me?
I mean, I know you're gay.
it's obvious.
Well, it's not that- it's not that obvious.
It's- Oh, yeah.
The way you talk and walk and dress
and your theatrical hand gestures.
I do not have
theatrical hand gestures.
Okay, maybe I am
moderately expressive.
But why would you
give me your number?
Oh, because
I want a gay friend.
Someone I can dish with, give me
guy advice and I can shop with.
Those are totally
offensive stereotypes.
We could go see Julia
Roberts movies together.
I know her, and she's as nice
as she seems on screen.
Shut up. Really?
She is, yeah.
Is she?
So you were pretending to be
straight and hitting on me?
It's just a stupid bar bet.
What-
My
boyfriend- Oh, he's here.
Bet me that I couldn't get
a beautiful woman's number.
And as a proud gay man,
I know it shouldn't matter,
but I- I just wish everyone
could find me attractive. Ohh.
Now he's going to get to gloat.
I guess I deserve it.
Hi.  Hi.
How's- How's it going?
Hello.
This is Katie.
And it turns out,
uh, well-
No, actually,
it doesn't turn out well.
Because I thought I finally
met a nice, funny guy ...
who is also hot!
And now he's
telling me he's gay?
He's like
the least gay person ...
I have ever met
in my entire life!
And I thought
he was the one!
And I even told
my mom about him!
You better cherish him!
Hello. Wow.
Are you sure you're gay? No.
- Cam.
- Yes.
Yes.
Look, you're gonna
find somebody ...
because you're
an amazing girl, Katie.
You're the whole package.
I just prefer somebody
who has one.
Okay.
Oh, my God.
That was a lot of girl tongue.
I think I need
a drink-a-doodle-doo.
What was that?
Hello, Haley.
How was your day?
I had no money,
no cell phone-
You're welcome.
What?
I listened to you.
I stopped coddling you.
And look. You overcame an obstacle.
Oh, yeah, I did.
I grew up normal
despite my crazy mom!
Well, that sounds like the
beginning of a great essay.
"Dear college"-
Oh, honey, if you get stuck,
let me know,
and I'll make you
sleep out in the yard.
- You're psychotic!
- Use spell check.
Salsa ]
Whoo!
Aaah!
Don't just sit there!
Get out here!
- I'm good. I'm good.
- Okay.
¡Hola! You're looking so good.
How long has it been?
We don't know each other.
Go away.
Fair enough.
¡Hola! You're looking so good.
How long has it been?
What was wrong
with that guy?
I would've danced with him.
He's got nice shoulders.
Oh, you know, salsa is
so intimate and sensual ...
that it feels wrong to do it with
somebody else that is not Jay.
Aw. Yeah, Darlene
feels the same way.
If I wasn't here, she'd
be holding up the wall.
Yeah. A wall of men.
You know, I think I should go
home to my loving husband ...
and pull him close and tell him
that I danced with 20 men.
He's not home.
He's in a dicey neighborhood,
worried about his car.
¡Ay, no!
Jay, you-
Mwah! What, are we
gonna kiss or dance?
Let's dance. Come, come.
I'm dead set against drugs.
Just say no and all that stuff.
But I thought-
just this once, for Gloria.
And if I was gonna make a complete ass
of myself, I didn't wanna remember it.
The big drug I gave him-
baby aspirin.
Orange flavored.
He could have chewed it.
How come you never
surprise me like that?
I do surprise you. No, you don't.
You never surprise me.
That's gonna be
a hell of a tree house.
Oh. Thanks.
I'm trying.
It's for my son,
but he's kind of lost interest.
It's kind of like my daughter
with the dog,
which is why
I'm the one ...
out here doing this.
Did you just move in?
Lived here eight years.
You?
Twelve.
- Huh.
Me and my friends, we built a
tree house when I was a kid.
We spent hours in that thing.
Loved it.
Me too.
You need any help?
Yes. A lot.
But I- I don't
wanna bother you.
Only thing bothering me is that
drunken Amish roof you got up there.
- Do you even have a level?
- I did.
But I might've gotten frustrated
and thrown it into your yard.
Let me find it. I'll be right over.
Thanks.
I'm Phil, by the way.
I'm Andre.
Nice to meet you, Phil.
Nice to meet you, Andre.
So I guess I was wrong when I said once
you get older, it's harder to make new friends.
Honey, the dude
in the tree is cool!
Andre, it turns out,
is an orthopedic surgeon,
handy with tools
and a great guy to hang out with.
Plus, he's a bad-ass black man
that gives me extra street cred.
That's his joke.
He's my brotha
from a different motha.
What was that?
Different-
That's not it.
What is it?
It's brotha from anotha motha.
Brotha from anotha motha.
Slow down.
Slow it down.
Brotha from anotha motha.
Forget it. Don't- Just don't say it.
Forget it.
English - US - PSDH