Whoa.
What's all this?
- Mom heard us say we were bored.
- Suckers.
She heard us from outside.
She has super good hearing,
like a Seeing Eye dog.
They have overdeveloped hearing
to make up for the fact-
Wait. The dogs aren't blind.
Wait. Are they?
No, that wouldn't make sense.
You're right. If I wait long enough,
she can get there by herself.
Quick, girls. Famous
Danny from Moonstruck.
Aiello.
Hey, Phil,
I'm glad I caught ya.
What's up ?
Uh, it's about
Steven and Stefan.
They want' to see that' house
on Briar again.
Really? I showed it to 'em five times.
Last time we were there,
I think they got mail.
Yeah, well, that's why I'm calling.
They hate upsetting people.
Unless, of course, it's me.
Then they don't mind waking me
at 7:00 a.m., asking me to call you.
It's no problem.
I'm just hanging around.
Kind of bored, really.
What?
Well, we did
our good deed for the day.
Yeah, for the enemy.
Don't they have enough?
It's been about a year since
we decided to adopt a boy.
Meanwhile, our friends Steven and Stefan
decided that they wanted a baby too.
Wonder where
they got that idea.
Well, we're still waiting,
but they already got their kid,
because they went through
a surrogate.
Which is all
they talk about.
Are you gonna keep doing that?
I might.
I have to go show a house. But first, what was
Elton John's sexual orientation in the '70s?
Bi.
- You've done that one before.
- And it never gets old.
Like the good
Captain Fantastic himself.
Hey, Claire, guess what? I'm sorry,
honey, I can't talk right now.
I told Bethenny I would take her to the airport.
I'm late, and she's gonna miss her flight.
Where are my keys?
Why is that chair still here?
I thought you and Luke were gonna
put it out on the sidewalk.
So you can't talk,
unless it's about my chores.
Why don't you just do it now
and you won't be so bored.
You heard that?
I hear everything.
That's for me.
Hey, Leon.
Nice buzz cut.
Yeah, for some people,
the shampoo doesn't work.
It only makes
the lice angry.
Nice to see you.
Oh, no. No.
Oh, God.
Um, Alex, do not move.
Haley, clean this up, okay?
Who fills a vase
with marbles?
Who doesn't see a vase
filled with marbles?
Who wants to hear
a bunch of plates crashing?
Phil! Honey, the girls
need you in the kitchen.
Thanks for the hat, Leon.
Kind of tickles.
Phil!
How much electricity
do we need to bring this back?
It's not rocket science. We're
only reanimating a squirrel.
Phil! Now!
# Hey, hey #
# Hey ##
Sounds great.
No, hang on.
Gloria, where's Manny?
Some neighborhood kids have
invited him to play football.
He said he was taking
his morning constitutional.
He's workin' on his go-kart,
but he'll be there.
Okay, see you then.
No, Manny cannot
go and play with those boys.
Margo is trying to get us
theater tickets for this afternoon.
Gloria, you and Manny
do enough together.
Let's let him decide.
Where's he walking?
I don't know. But according to
the song he was singing,
he was going to
the sunny side of the street.
I cannot express to you enough
how bad this kid needs football.
Mom, look what I found!
Number 99!
When Manny was five,
we didn't have much,
we were on our own,
so we always dreamed
of winning the lottery.
We figured if we collected
100 lucky heads-up pennies ...
and bought a ticket with them,
we couldn't lose.
But now, I have a wonderful
husband, a beautiful home.
I feel like I already
won the lottery.
So I can keep
whatever we win?
I think no.
I found most of them.
Can you put this in the jar
with the others?
A y, I forgot. What is the
combination to your safe?
Uh-
I'll just come with you.
Oh, yes, 'cause that's how this arrangement works.
I take money from you.
Hello.
Oh, hi, Margo. No, no,
she just ran upstairs.
Listen, about these
theater tickets.
Don't knock yourself out
tryin' to- Oh, you did.
Well, sorry to do this last minute,
but they can't go.
No, Manny has a football game,
so-
Jay, could you steep my tea?
I cannot express to you enough
how much this kid needs football.
And that is the whole house.
Again.
I love it,
but I just don't love it.
Do you love it? I love it.
I absolutely love it.
I'm just not sure if I'm
in love with it. Oh, yeah.
We have an expression around the office
for when a sale just isn't happening-
commission impossible.
Maybe for some people.
Not sure if I mentioned it
before,
but the house does come with a hookup
for a European washing machine.
Oh, I love that.
Oh, so sorry.
It's the boss.
- Hey.
- Hi. I'm on my way home.
I've been calling Haley, but nobody's answering.
ls everything okay there?
Everything here is great.
Oh, thank God. Did you
put the chair out front?
Not yet. Honey, you're gonna
miss the trash pickup.
Don't worry. if they don't
take it, someone else will.
Who is gonna pick up
that ratty chair off our lawn?
Are you kidding?
It's in great shape.
Super cozy. People are
always commenting on it.
Trust me, it'll be gone
by the end of the day.
- Please just do it now.
- I can't.
I'm so sorry.
When I'm done with these clients,
I'll call Luke and Leon.
I know I can
talk them into it.
We are not losing this house
to Luke and Leon.
What do you mean, "call Luke and Leon"?
Aren't you at home?
No, I left
right before you did.
Phil, the hou-
The-The kids.
Oh, God, the squirrel.
Hello?
We'll take it.
Oh.
Commission ... accomplished.
So how great is your life right now, huh?
A new house, new baby.
Stefan's Propecia's kicking in.
Oh. That's him.
He's on his way.
He texted "O.M.W." We try to keep our texts
short when we're driving with the baby.
Oh, well, what wonderful
parents you are.
You guys hate us
a little bit, don't you?
No. God, no.
Yeah, just a little.
Have you thought
about surrogacy?
At least you'd be
making a baby,
instead of waiting around for some
pregnant morn to maybe pick you.
Well, we considered it, but how
do you decide which one will-
Where's Lily?
Sleeping.
Ice the cupcake?
That you couldn't
say in front of Lily?
Well, then she'd want a cupcake.
Yeah.
- But that's the beauty of the swirl.
- The swirl?
You both donate.
They mix it up, fertilize the egg,
you never know
who the father is.
Ooh, that's Stefan.
You know, maybe we should
think about the swirl.
Well, I-l didn't think Surrogacy
was for us, but, you know-
'Cause one of us would
feel left out.
Yeah, but if you don't know
whose it is-
Sorry we're late.
Guys, meet Rocco.
Rocco or cocoa?
- Look at him out there.
- Oh, honey, this is so exciting.
Go ahead! Attaboy!
Go! Go ahead!
Go, Manny! Run!
I knew Gloria would find out
I lied about those tickets,
but I figured
when she saw Manny out there,
playing with all those other
kids, she'd thank me.
That's what I figured.
Go, go!
What the hell's he doin'?
Run, Manny, run!
Mom, number 100!
Now we have the money-
Oh, thank God.
Nobody's dead.
Or we're all dead.
- How many plates did we lose?
- None.
Luke and Haley used cookie sheets to
clear a path through the marbles for me.
- Where are the marbles?
- Right here.
- Oh, Haley!
- I put glue on 'em so it doesn't happen again.
- What about the chair?
- Leon and I rolled it outside on some skateboards.
Oh.  The squirrel.
You think I was going to
let that happen?
These kids are going to survive.
They are the best of me and Phil.
Luke using the skateboards, Haley
gluing the marbles- That is pure Phil.
Alex keeping everyone in line?
Pure me.
Sometimes I worry
no one's gonna like Alex.
There you go, buddy.
Thank you.
Uh- What? You need anything?
I'll get it.
Steak sauce.
But it's okay.
It's probably good for me
to move around.
Oh, Jay, it's so nice to see you
take care of him like that.
Why are you surprised? He's our kid.
We take care of each other
in this family.
I want to kill you.
Wild guess- Margo.
Let me explain.
There is no excuse.
This is sounding private.
I'm gonna get out of here.
So that's why you were
being so nice.
You lied
to my friend.
You made Manny
play the American football.
It is your fault that
he got stampeded.
Or is it your fault?
He stopped to pick up a penny,
for God's sake.
Be careful
what you say, Jay.
You're skating on thin
eggshells right now.
I tried to get him out there
with kids his own age,
which is what he should
be doin'-
And not spending another
afternoon with his mommy.
If you have a problem with the way
Manny's being raised, you talk to me!
I am. I don't want to hear it!
Phil, you really
didn't have to do this.
I sold a house today because of you two.
The least I can do is buy you dinner.
I saw that house.
It is gorgeous.
I know. Yes. We're
real happy for them.
They showed me a picture of the baby.
How adorable is that little guy?
Yes, we're real happy
for them.
Okay, you might want to
slow down there.
I'm playing
a new drinking game.
It's called "Every time I'm depressed,
I take a drink."
That game exists.
It's called alcoholism.
Oh, I'm sorry.
You're right.
I'm-I'm wallowing,
and it's not cute.
- To happier things.
- Yes.
To happier things.
Happier things.
There you go. Yes.
I remember the first few drinks,
and, urn, after that, the
night's just bits and pieces.
I want to do something I never
do- brag about my kids.
Today, they were resourceful.
They were responsible. They-
Put 40% down.
It was worth showing the house
five times and waiting-
Almost a year. Seriously!
Who do you have to-
Blow. That's really hot. Why don't you
let it cool down and try some of the-
Mexican! The baby
is clearly Mexican.
So, you know,
the swirl is out.
Oh, it's enough
to make you lose-
Track. Is this my fourth
drink, or is it my fourth?
I just said fourth twice, didn't I?
I did, didn't I?
I think we're gonna need four cabs.
Two! Two!
You made me!
L-I vaguely remember
someone crying.
If we ever did surrogacy, I
would want you to be the donor.
Mm-mmm. You're so smart.
You're so handsome.
Oh, stop it. It should be you.
You're so fun.
- You're so talented.
- Okay.
It's not fair.
I love you both so much.
If you could have a baby that was a mix of the
two of you, I would love that baby so much.
- Stop it.
- Oh, that is so sweet.
I meant it.
That is so sweet.
Oh, my God, you guys,
we could do this.
We could do this. We could make a baby
that is half Tucker and half Pritchett.
Are you saying what I think
you're saying?
Yeah.
Cloning?
No, no. I'm saying ...
I give the egg.
Oh!
Yeah, I give the egg.
That's the Pritchett side.
And then Cam,
you're the father, right?
And then we just, like, mix it and put
it in a- like, a surrogate lady thing,
and then, bang,
we have a baby.
Oh! Are-Are you serious?
You would do that?
I would be honored.
You guys.
You guys, if there's one
thing I have learned today,
it's the pleasure of looking at
your children and seeing both-
both of you in there,
and I want you to have
that experience.
- We need that. We want that.
- Yeah.
And something else.
- Guys, I make really good babies.
- Yes.
- I have magic eggs or something.
- They're, like, golden.
- Oh, gosh.
Oh, Phil, I don't- What do you-
What do you say about this?
I think we're all
having a baby!
Table hug!
Sweet potato fries!
What have I done?
I know.
Oh.
What was I thinking?
I just get drunk, and I bring
a baby into the world?
That would be
four for four.
I can't go through with it.
Don't panic. You haven't
donated anything yet.
Besides, what are the chances
your eggs even work?
What are the chances we can
pretend I never said that?
It's weird.
it's my brother.
And then there would be this baby over there
that's my baby, but it's not my baby-
That actually sounds good.
Just say that.
We're gonna see 'em for brunch
in two hours over at your dad's.
Ooh, that seems soon ...
and-and hard.
What if- What if
I blame it on you?
What if we say that
you're not okay with it?
" No!
Are you really okay with another
man fertilizing your wife's egg?
- Of course not. That's creepy.
- Yes.
Plus, what if you and Cam make
a better baby than we did?
It's settled.
Phil says no.
Like they're really gonna
believe that I overruled you.
Oh, right.
Come on.
Mmm.
They're gonna be crushed.
They've waited so long
for this baby.
Maybe they're having
second thoughts too.
Look. This is what my baby
with Claire would look like.
What is this? What?
Okay, well, I found a Web site
where couples can upload pictures,
and then it shows 'em what their
baby would look like.
This is Gloria and I.
Couldn't resist.
Wow.
That-That looks
exactly like Manny.
Like-Like weirdly so.
Wait, what's
this other picture?
Don't be jealous.
But this is me
and Justin Timberlake.
Cam, we have a problem.
Oh, what, you can talk about Ryan Gosling
all day, but the moment I say something-
No, no, no.
About this baby.
I don't think I can do it.
What? Why?
Why? it's perfect.
It's our chance to have a baby
that's part me, part you.
No, no, it's part you
and part Claire.
I'm nowhere in there. And
it's not like I can pretend.
It's- She's not some egg donor
that we don't know. it's Claire.
You know, we see her
all the time.
And what are we supposed to tell the baby?
"Say hi to your Aunt Mommy."
- Adorable.
- No, not adorable.
Appalachian.
Okay, I'm-I'm sorry, Cam.
Jay says that I'm smothering
Manny, but I'm just enjoying him.
I mean, they're only gonna
be boys for a short time.
Best time ever
in this house!
I'm uncomfortable
with this, Phil.
The manual specifically
says "No towing."
There are two types
of people in this world-
people who follow the manual and
people who stick it to the manu-
That hurt!
Hi.
- Manny, what happened?
- Football injury.
My mom will "yell" you
all about it.
Hola, Lily. Does my little
princess want a cookie?
Oh, well, you know,
maybe just one.
She's already had her sugar limit for today.
How can you tell?
¡Ay! Okay, Lily.
Hey.
Hey, you two.
So, where-
Oh, where are the kids?
Oh, Haley's driving them
over separately.
Ohh.
Big girl now.
That's right.  Yeah.
So, that was
so fun last night.
So fun. Yeah. We
had a great night.
Yes.
We should get that-
Jinx.
We're goin' this way, so-
350 for 30.
See you in a bit.
That looks delicious.
I cannot tell them.
I cannot break their hearts.
So you're gonna have Cam's baby just
to keep things from being weird?
Um, what?
You and Uncle Cam
are having a baby?
Kids, shh. There was a discussion about the
possibility of your mom donating an egg ...
so that the guys
could have a baby.
But we decided
it was not a good idea.
Why? Because
Lily's such a mess?
For a lot of reasons.
They have to-
But we can agree that she's a
disaster as a human being.
- I think it's a great idea.
- Yeah.
It's a really beautiful offer, Mom.
I'm impressed.
Oh, my God. Cam!
They told the kids already, and
they seem to be totally into it.
Is it just me? Am I the only
one that thinks this is weird?
Maybe it's not weird. Maybe we're pioneers.
No, we're hardly pioneers.
You have three different hair dryers
for different types of weather.
Maybe it's just gonna take some
time to get used to the idea.
What idea?
Oh.
Um, well, Jay-
Cam.
Claire has-
No. I- I just don't think my dad's
really ready for this conversation, so-
Stop acting like
I'm some stodgy old coot.
I've grown.  Okay.
Um, Jay, Claire has offered
to give us one of her eggs,
so we can have a baby that's
half Pritchett, half Tucker.
That's unnatural.
I'm against it.
Oh, surprise, surprise.
Jay's against something.
Cam and Claire want to
have a baby together.
Eww!
You're not gonna do that.
It's not
your decision, Dad.
You're not thinking straight.
And you're not in charge.
Okay, Claire and I
are adults.
If we want this to happen,
it's-it's gonna happen.
So much for second thoughts.
Young lady, I need to
have a talk with you.
I don't- Now?  No!
You don't get to tell everyone
how to live their lives,
that boys cannot spend time
with their mommies ...
or that brothers and sister
can't make babies.
So you're all for this? No, it's a
freak show, but it's their freak show.
So this is
happening again.
Well, I'm not gonna not do it
'cause my dad thinks I shouldn't.
I'm not following. We're not doing
it 'cause I don't want to do it.
What we're not doing is not doing it
'cause he doesn't want us to do it!
Just say baby or no baby.
Isn't it enough this family
spends a lot of time together?
Now we have to inbreed.
Okay, Dad. it's not technically
inbreeding. it's, um-
For the record, I think what
my mom is doing is very brave.
I like it. I've always kind of
wanted a half-brother, half-cousin.
- Really? Always?
- I mean, if you think about it-
I disagree
with you about inbreeding, young lady.
I would like to make a small presentation.
If everyone could-
Once the neighbors find out,
and they will-
Oh, wow. When was the last
time we talked under a table?
Dad and Gloria's wedding reception.
Oh, yeah.
Um, mmm-
I love you. You know that.
But I can't do this.
No, no, neither can I.
Really?
Yeah. Are you serious?
You can't-
Oh, God, I'm so relieved.
I'm sorry.
L-I- Oh, I am so sorry
I led us down this road.
No, no, Claire.
Don't be. Don't be.
It was generous and thoughtful,
just like you.
How could I not want
those qualities in my child?
Ohh.
Oh, come here.
Good brother. So this
is really happening?
What if it is, Dad? Yeah, what if we love
each other and this is a beautiful thing?
Okay, it's our decision.
it's not yours. Yeah.
So- baby, no baby?
No.
Mm-mmm.
You okay?
Oh, yeah, I'm fine.
Oh, I know
it's been hard on you.
Hey, what if we went out
for a nice dinner tonight?
Oh, that'd be fun. Should
I call the sitter? Yeah.
You know what I was thinking today?
What about Luke?
Oh, he's so good with her,
the way he looks at her.
Oh, my God, Cam.
Oh.
She's organizing
her things.
Look at how she's dressed.
Oh.
We didn't make her,
but she sure is us.
Hey, Lily. It might make
more sense with the shoes-
Mitchell.
I like what she did with the dolls though.
Play as you will.
It's nice.
The bent one, remember?
One of the first ones we found.
It was at the bottom
of the gutter in the street.
A y, yes. We put the gum at the
bottom of your walking stick.
Ay, look at this one,
the green one.
- The one we found at the floor of my taxi.
- Your taxi?
Yes. Before I had somebody running my life
for me, I used to drive a taxi at night.
Manny would sleep
in the seat next to me.
One time, I had to hit
the brakes so hard ...
that he fell into the floor,
and he found the penny.
Pretty lucky, huh?
Eight years. I can't believe
we're finally done.
Me, either.
Come. Let's go
get your lottery ticket.
Gloria, I think you
made a mistake here.
What did I do now?
I've counted these, and
you've only got 96 pennies.
Are you sure?
'Fraid so.
I guess you're gonna
have to keep lookin'.
Dang it!
I counted those.
See for yourself.
And now we upload
your picture.
This is fun.
Yeah. And in just a few short moments,
thanks to the magic of technology,
we'll know what our
baby actually looks like.
No, no.
What happened? What is that?
Did you put one of us in
upside down?
No, that's actually- Okay, I don't
want to see this anymore. Turn it off.
Oh, it's not turning off. Throw
something over it, then. Oh, God!
Yeah, well, we played God,
and look what we brought forth.
Daddies,
what are you looking at?
- Maybe it wasn't that bad.
- No, no.
It's possible that
we overreacted.
Yeah. Maybe our expectations
were just a little too high.
The little guy had some
cute features, huh?
Of course he did. it's us.
It can't be that bad.
Let's just take a-
English - US - PSDH