There she is.
The old library.
Had some late nights
in there.
Some of 'em
I even spent studying.
Don't tell your morn.
And maybe don't tell me.
Oh.
College!
He was shielding his eyes from the sun.
Knew it when I hit it.
Phil is taking Haley
to visit his alma mater.
Loved college.
Mmm. We are hoping some of that
enthusiasm rubs off on her.
Go Bullfrogs!
Dogs. Bulldogs.
I feel like you do that on purpose.
Mm-mmm.
No, it's just I say "bull," and I
can't remember if it's frogs or dogs.
When I talk to my old friends from
college, do we croak or do we bark?
I got it.
Hello.
Wow.
No way. Haley, no way!
Check it out!
After a few beers, my buds and I
would jump on these lunch trays ...
and race down
this same hill.
Hop on.
I don't want to hop on.
Seriously. You'll get the giggles.
I don't want the giggles.
Hey, honey.
Hawk the trip going?
So good.
Go Bullfrogs!
It's dogs!
Oh, sorry.
- How's Haley doing?
- She's-
She's loving it.
Ready! I showed
her the student union.
Five, six, seven, eight.
We visited the dorms.
We sat in on a class.
I really think she's starting to
see what college has to offer.
Oh, hang on, Claire.
Go Bulldogs!
# Hey, hey #
# Hey ##
Manny, who is this Bella girl,
and why is her name
all over your notebook?
Bella's no girl, Mom.
She has recently blossomed,
like a purple lilac in April.
What do you mean, she blossom?
Like the puberty?
Yep.
I'll get it.
Hey, Gloria, your
show's about to start.
Record it.
No, the DVR's filling up.
Let's just watch
and get it over with.
Gloria's always saying we
should do more stuff together.
So I agreed to watch this crazy
Colombian soap opera she loves.
Fuego y hielo.
Which apparently is Spanish
for "big hair and yelling."
Fire and Ice.
It's about human suffering.
I relate to it.
I'm just saying, the guy's a judge.
He could put a shirt on.
A y, what is that?
Oh, nothing.
That doesn't look like a nothing.
What is inside?
Oh, it's just something
I bought
I'm gonna go open it
in my room.
I don't like this.
Manny has never
kept a secret from me.
Don't worry about it. What
do you think it could be?
Well, right now, I'm a little worried
it could be the rest of my evening.
Mwah! Bye-bye. Love you.
Hey, Claire, listen. Uh,
if you want, some of the moms ...
are going to stay and watch Gone with
the Wind in my new screening room.
I got Pinot.
I would love to, but I'm
not feeling that great, so-
Probably just gonna go home
and rest.
Plus, I've seen that movie.
No, I never saw
Gone with the Wind.
But I have two kids at sleepovers,
and Haley's out of town with Phil.
That means I have
one night to myself,
which happens once every never.
I am not spending it
with some gossipy mom ...
who was mean to me
in high school.
I need a fun night out.
What the hell is this?
No, I asked you guys
for a fun night out, not this.
I need music and dancing
and secondhand smoke.
Oh, please give this place a chance.
It's a great value.
The room is so cozy, and the
pot pies are to die for.
Are you really comfortable
with what you just said?
Come on. What happened to the party
people who took me to a rave?
And I got to wear a tube top, and I stuffed
cash in a caged go-go boy's Speedo.
We're still party people.
Oh, Joanne, before I
forget, can I get a punch?
One away from a free pot pie.
- If that was your gay card, it would be revoked.
- Okay, you know what, Claire?
You're being a little
"high school you."
I am sorry, Mitchell,
but I get one free night,
and I can't spend it at a place that is
a proud supporter of Wilson Elementary.
- We all need to give back, Claire.
- Oh, give me back my night.
Okay, well, Longines did invite
us to a boutique opening.
You know, cocktails, deejay.
it'll be whole scene though.
A scene? A scene is perfect.
That's great.
I will get in the car before you guys
change your mind. Come on. Let's go.
So does that mean
no pot pies?
Uh- Hey, Joanne,
two number nines to go.
Was I wrong?
Are these not the best wings you've
ever had in your life? Oh, my God!
And you didn't want
to get 40.
Oh, and by the way, this is
just the start of your evening.
Next up, it's over to the quad for a
musical interlude from Tenors, Anyone?
It's an all-male singing group.
Got it.
Oh, hey! Oh, hey, weren't you
on my tour this morning?
Yeah, I'm Haley, and
this is my- Big brother.
You bought it for a second!
How are you?
Oh. That's-
Okay.
Anyway, you know what? There is a
student mixer going on tonight.
If you want to go, me and a bunch
of girls are gonna head over there.
Oh, uh-
Know what? That's okay.
My dad's got this whole thing
planned, but thank you anyway.
No problem. Well, it
was nice meeting you.
Nice meeting you.
How fun is this?
Just me and you.
I was a little nervous you wouldn't see
what's so special about this place.
Not that I'm pushing you to come here. You
know, you're gonna make your own decisions.
You want to go with them, don't you?
No, we're doing our thing.
Yeah, quick, before they leave.
Are you sure?
Go. I can handle it.
You're not the first girl
to leave me at this table ...
with a plateful
of chicken wings.
I'm kidding.
Wish I was kidding.
You weren't supposed
to hear that.
Have fun.
Okay.
Love you.
Nose job. Ooh.
Butt lift. Last summer, that thing
was four inches off the ground.
What do they do with all
the butt they take out?
I have a theory.
Oh, hell!
Here comes my ex.
Who, Randolph?
Marcus?
- Lamichael?
- No, Matt.
Oh.
I gotta go!
Drama! Love it!
This is what I wanted.
Who needs a drink? I could
use a little seltzer water.
More bubbly, Claire? I will
be after I get a drink.
See, that's what
gay is supposed to be like.
Okay, I don't know about you, but I got
about five minutes of fabulous left in me.
Yeah. In my mind,
I'm already in our kitchen ...
and I'm watching my pot pie
rotate in the microwave.
Okay, okay.
When did hats come back?
That one's come back about eight times.
Pick a side of the room, lady!
All right, there's, like, a
thousand people waiting for wine.
I want to try on
a couple of dresses,
and then Julian here is going to
take us to a club across town.
I think we're gonna go home.
What? Why? it's 9:30.
It's 9:30?
When did you two
become such old women?
First you take me to that
senior center for porridge,
and now you can't even stay up
past Luke's bedtime?
It's Friday. We get tired on Fridays.
We get very tired.
I have three children.
I have been tired since 2005.
Let's rally.
You're my ride. If you want to
stay out, I can take you home.
Really?
Of course.
Okay.
All right, girls, go home, roll up
your hair, clap out the lights,
'cause this guy,
who I just met,
is gonna show me a good time.
Okay, well, if he was straight, this
would be just like high school.
This is ridiculous.
She's obviously got a pistol
under that poncho.
How do you watch this stuff?
He's been up there for more than one hour.
I can't stand it.
Who's been up there? Reinaldo's doin'
the dishes right in front of her.
Manny, in his bedroom.
Gloria, are you
even watching this?
I'm doin' this for you.
What does he has in that box
that he cannot show to me?
Little boys are supposed to
keep secrets from their mothers.
Wait. The judge
just peeked through the window.
Is he interested in Celia now?
She could be his daughter.
I bet it's a birthday gift for me.
Yeah, that sounds right.
What's he saying?
I've never seen him this mad.
Wait a minute.
I already found my birthday
gift underneath his bed.
It's a giant hat.
When did hats
came back, anyway?
Now she's reaching
under the poncho.
Like she's gonna shoot Reinaldo.
He's the main character, right?
That's it.
I'm going up there.
Wait, Gloria, no, don't go.
Why not? Think about it.
Thirteen-year-old boy.
Talks about girls all day long.
We have more security on these
computers than the Pentagon.
What do you think
he's doin' up there, alone?
Do you think
he ordered some movies?
Movies, magazines.
Whatever the hell.
How dare do you say that,
Jay?
He's a little boy!
He's just a boy.
I don't want to talk to you.
I'm gonna take a walk.
Gloria, come on.
Come back.
I know you're not mad at me.
You just-
Oh! What'd she do?
Reinaldo!
Oh! Wang chung!
Pay UP, gentlemen!
Oh, yes!
Thank you!
Really? That's so nice.
Another pitcher,
my good woman.
Claire would have killed me
if she'd known ...
that I let Haley go off alone while I
chilled in a bar with some undergrads,
but I happen
to trust my daughter.
Also, I was tracking her location
with the G.P.S. on her phone.
Fellas, Cedar and Los Alamos.
That's, uh-
- Pi Chi house?
- Pi Chi?
Come on. Why
is my Bluetooth not working?
Oh, God, it's Longines.
He's gonna be so mad at us.
Hey, Longe, don't
be mad at us for leaving.
I went back to our
spot, and everybody was gone.
Who does that to a sister?
We're sorry,
but the sitter called,
and Lily
was running a fever, so-
We feel even worse about dumping
Claire on you and your hot date.
Who is gorgeous, by the way.
Seems super funny too.
Perfect for you.
Please.
I wish that was a date.
He is my trainer, and he's straight.
What? Julian's straight?
Oh, I love it when a straight person
and a gay person go out together.
I'd love it a lot more
if he was gay.
Oh, my God.
This isn't our car.
What?
This isn't our Prius.
They must've given us the
wrong one at the valet.
That's why the Bluetooth
isn't working.
We stole a car. Are you serious?
What's happening?
Oh, we stole a car.
Uh, we gotta go.
We did not steal a car, Cam.
It was given to us.
Why are you giving me attitude?
You're the one that stole a car!
How is this a stolen car? How?
I don't know! I'm confused!
Do you have an aspirin?
This isn't my car!
Mmm. Mm-mmm.
Mmm. Hey, Lukey.
Hi. What's goin' on?
Oh, I don't have-
I'll check.
I have it.
Well, I could bring it by and
meet you outside in 20 minutes.
No, sweet-
Out-Outside, sweetie.
Okay. Bye-We-
Do you mind swinging by
my kid's sleepover?
I gotta give him his retainer.
It's on the way to the club.
Sure. No problem.
Oh, you are so sweet.
Holy pythons, Batman!
Do you ever leave the gym?
Uh, no. Actually, I'm a
trainer and a masseur.
Oh, my God.
I'm gonna have to try out
that second one.
Zip, please.
I gotta say, this night
is turning out to be ...
a lot more fun
than I expected.
I've got two kids at sleepovers
and one upstate with Daddy.
The fun is just beginning.
Unbelievable.
The valet gave our car away to
someone, like, an hour and a half ago.
You know what that means.
Our pot pies could be anywhere by now.
They probably went home.
If we knew their address, maybe we
could see if our car was there.
Oh, yeah, and how do you propose
we do that?
Calculating route home.
Oh, you're good. Oh, and look.
Only .6 miles away.
Prepare to turn night
in 500 feel.
Notice how she didn't wait until
a?er the turn to tell me, Cam?
Really? This? Now?
I'm just-
Oh, look, they went to see Jay-Z. We
almost went to see Jay-Z, didn't we?
No, no, no. 'Cause, remember?
It started at 8:30.
Oh, yeah, which meant he wouldn't
have gone on till 10:00.
- And that's a parking nightmare.
- Oh, and those stairs.
Okay,
I'm hearing it now.
Is Claire right?
Are we in a rut?
Oh, we might be, especially
compared to these people.
Look at this.
Cancún luggage tickets.
A parking pass to Yosemite.
A triathlon bib.
This is living.
No, but, you know,
we have Lily, okay?
You can't do that with a child.
They have a car seat.
Okay, fine, we're in a rut.
Destination ahead
in 900 feet.
You know, maybe we just need to be
around more stimulating people.
Well, we're gonna be
in about 900 feet.
It's not the craziest idea.
They seem like fun people.
Yeah, and maybe we can be new couples
friends with them, you know?
We can go out to concerts, try exciting
new food, maybe do some luxury camping.
Hitch our wagon to their star and see
how fast they spice up our life.
You have arrived.
I believe we have.
You dumb son of a bitch!
Oh, my God, what's happening?
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
What's happening?
I can't believe
you came back here,
you filthy, cheating pig!
No, no, back up.
- Back up, I said!
- I'm trying! We are in a rut.
Really? You want to talk
about that right now?
No, we are stuck.
We're in an actual rut.
We're stuck.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God!
We are victim of a hate crime right now.
Go! Go! Oh, my God.
Oh, no, you don't. Dad!
What are you doing here?
What's this, buddy?
Ginger ale.
Oh, really?
Cause it smells-
Okay, it smells like ginger ale,
but that doesn't prove anything.
What the hell?
We are leaving.
I'm having a nice time!
With this clown?
And by the way, it's a little cliche to pick
someone who looks exactly like your dad.
I got your number, Pi Chi.
I know you.
Yeah, you do.
This is Ben Ford. He's in my class.
He's visiting too.
You were my T-ball coach.
My dad's your doctor.
He's right over there.
What is wrong with you?
Are you trying to ruin college
for me before I even get here?
No, I'm not.
I am so sorry.
You are not a clown. You are
an excellent backup shortstop.
Alecia, Bruce.
Go Bullfrogs- Dogs!
Go Bulldogs. Claire!
Wow. Really.
No, it's just a shock, is all.
Jay.
So Celia is carrying
the judge's baby.
No wonder she shot him.
She's hormonal.
- Who are you talking to?
- The housekeeper.
Maria, I've gotta go.
Thanks a lot.
- Jay, I need you to talk to Manny.
- What?
If he's doing what you think he's
doing, then he needs to talk to a man.
I don't want him
to be ashamed of anything.
Then you don't want to send me in there.
But what if he has questions?
What if he doesn't know how-
Gloria-
Gloria, whatever he's going through,
he can work it out himself.
Help! I'm stuck!
Ay, no. Jay, go! I beg of
you, go, go, go! Gloria-
I'm extremely reluctant
to do this.
Please hurry!
Ay, no. I cannot look at this.
What the hell?
I can't get down, Jay!
What? What
happened to Manny?
Ay, somebody
say something to me!
Gloria, it's okay.
Come in.
Okay.
- He was hanging from that bar up there.
- What? Why?
What do you have on your head?
It's a weighted helmet to
stretch me so I can get taller.
Whoa! Manny, why do you
have to get tall now?
Love, Mom. Why else?
I lost Bella to Durkas because,
in her words, "He's tall."
Everybody else
is getting taller but me.
You think it's the coffee? No.
Maybe, but- But hanging downside
up is not gonna help you.
The Web site said it would.
Listen, Manny, you're already
intelligent and beautiful and funny.
If you get tall, you're
going to have everything,
and those poor boys are not gonna
have anything to compete with you.
Look at this.
You have a mark
in your head now.
I'm gonna go get you
some ice, okay?
That's a lot of pretty words,
but they don't help me tomorrow.
Sorry, kid.
Just one of those things.
You get taller
when you get taller.
Why don't you
get ready for bed?
Ah, geez.
You know, when I was your age, I
started workin' out to get the girls.
- You think that would help?
- Yeah.
So tomorrow,
we start workin' out.
Okay?
Maybe I'll even show you a few pull-ups
on, uh, this bad boy here, huh?
You see that?
Pretty soon, that's how strong
you're gonna be.
Thanks, Mom. Shh! I don't
want them to know I was here.
Okay. Oh, Claire, I
thought that was you.
Thank God. Come in.
I can't, 'cause I'm sick, remember?
Sorry.
My DVD playerjust broke, and none of
us know how Gone with the Wind ends.
- But you saw it, right?
- Is that Claire?
- Yeah.
- Can you tell us what happened?
Uh, I could, but I don't want
to ruin it for you.
Claire, just tell us.
Just tell us.
Come on.
Um-
Scarlett is really mad
at Clark Gable because, um,
he's done just so-
so many bad things.
And didn't he, um, burn down
a farm or something?
Claire, have you been drinking?
Um, I had a hot toddy.
Made one for my throat, so-
Pretty dressed up
for a night in bed, right?
Yeah, I-l just threw on the first
thing I could find when Luke called.
- It was just right there on the chair.
- She has a stamp on her hand.
Okay. All right. Before we bust out
the pitchforks and the torches,
may I remind you that I've driven
every one of your children home,
and heimliched
at least one, Bethenny.
Hi.  Hello.
This is totally inappropriate,
but could I use your bathroom?
Sorry.
You kept pushing the drinks.
It's- Friend.
Gay friend. Gay.
I'm not gay.
Yes, you are.
I'm not gay. I'm-I'm French.
You thought I was gay?
Are you serious right now?
Are you? You've been throwing
yourself at me all night.
N-No. No. I have not.
- Bethenny, grab the Pinot.
- Bethenny, do not grab the Pinot.
You undressed in front of me.
You squeezed my arm.
You asked me for a massage.
What was all that?
That was- That was me safely
objectifying a gay person.
Wow, Claire.
When I wrote "Don't ever change" in your
yearbook, I didn't mean it like this.
Oh, ease up, Holly.
Okay, I lied. I lied.
But I get one night to myself,
and I just wanted to spend it
with some fun gay people.
It's not my fault this one
decided to be straight.
I've always been straight.
Oh, you don't get to talk!
I took fashion advice
from you.
Oh, my God, do I even
look good in this dress?
No, not you.
- It's really short, isn't it?
- it's short.
Yeah.
Please! Please just listen
to me for one second.
Go away!
Stop following me.
Hey, you want to tell me why
you're bothering this younglady?
Oh, no, no, no, no, Officer.
This is my daughter. Tell him.
Tonight, I don't know who you are.
She's-She's joking.
I'm not dangerous.
In fact, I helped to put
all the lights on this path.
Twenty years ago, some friends
and I took back the night, so-
I think I just-
I embarrassed her a little.
A little? That sweatshirt
embarrasses me a little.
Yep, that's a daughter.
Tonight was insane. Why did
you have to act like that?
You were at that party. I see
you talking to frat boys, and-
isn't that why we're here?
So I can experience college?
I mean, what are you gonna
do when I actually go?
I don't know.
Freak out, I think.
Look.
Your whole life,
my job's been to protect you.
A job I kind of love.
And I feel like I'm being forced
into early retirement.
I just needed to find you
and make sure you were okay-
for as long
as I still get to do that.
It's just like you-
Piss me off,
then say something sweet.
I'm not leaving
until the fall.
Maybe by then I can figure out how
to put a force field around you.
I've been working on that one
since the first time ...
I tried to fasten you
into your car seat.
I pinched
your chunky little thigh.
Aw.
Even though you basically
just called me fat.
So, is it really fun?
What?
No.
We all struggle
with limitations.
Some we're willing to accept-
You know, I just want to be home,
reading on opposite ends of the sofa.
And some we're not. I'm
so embarrassed I did that.
I'm just so happy
that that was all it was.
Why? What'd you think
I was doing?
It's never too late
to grow in life.
Oh, my God!
"Thanks to our patented
Lengthenator,
you can increase your height
by up to four inches."
I cannot believe he spent
$50 in this thing. I know.
He could've got a two-year
subscription to Playboy for that.
He's not getting the Playboy ever!
Ow!
He's a little boy!
Wouldn't it be great
if we woke up tomorrow,
and our car had
found its way home?
I feel that's not the way
it's gonna happen.
Happened on the farm one time.
A tornado scooped up one of our
calves, dropped it who knows where.
Six months later, a full-grown cow
comes walking up the driveway.
Same markings, same moo.
That night, we- We ate like kings.
Yeah.
Okay, I've told it before.
Oh, my gosh, it's our car!
I see you've met my wife.
English - US - PSDH