We have to tell him.
I hope he's okay.
Walt, our elderly
next-door neighbor, died.
He and Luke were pretty close,
so we have to tell him.
I'm a little nervous
about it.
I think we should break it
to him slowly. Like how?
Well, first we'd say, "Luke, your friend Walt has a cold.
You shouldn't go over there."
Next day, "Bad news.
WaIt's in the hospital,
but he's still crackin' jokes
with the nurses."
Next day, "They're trying an experimental drug.
Fingers crossed."
Next day, "His body rebelled.
He's in a coma."
Next day, he rallies.
Next day, coma.
Next day, coma. Next day, coma.
Next day, eye flutter-
Stop. Just stop. Stop.
Oh. Luke, we have some bad news for you.
it's about Walt.
I'm afraid ...
he passed away.
Um, it happened yesterday.
He finished writing an angry letter
to the Postmaster General,
and he just fell asleep.
Okay.
It was very peaceful.
Not the letter.
That was full of threats, but-
it's okay
to be sad, honey.
You two were
really good friends.
It must be quite a shock
to hear that WaIt's dead.
Um, so do you want to
talk about it, or-
I'm okay. Can I get back to
my video game? It's paused.
Oh. Um, sure.
Yeah, buddy.
Come here.
How weird was that?
I know.
Crazy weird.
It's like he had
no feelings at all.
I'm more worried about the one you showed.
What's with all the smiling?
What are you
talking about?
That grin. "WaIt's dead."
You looked like the Joker.
I didn't smile. You did. it's
like a weird coping mechanism.
You did the same thing
when you told him his hamster died.
I don't know what you
thought you saw, Phil,
but our child just got some terrible
news and had absolutely no reaction.
Doesn't that concern you?
Yeah. He probably just
needs time to process it.
Hmm. Do you think?
Yeah, honey.
Death is a profound thing to deal with at any age.
We all manage it differently.
Some people lock up
their feelings.
Others reach out for comfort,
finding some way to reaffirm
their connection to life.
Are you joking?
# Hey, hey #
# Hey ##
Haley?
Hey, Gloria.
I was driving by and saw this
outside your door, so here.
Thank you.
No problem.
Hey. So, since
I'm already here,
my friend was going to have a pool
party tonight, but he got sick.
Could we have it here? Mm, good
thing that you saw this paper,
- or if not, you would have never been able to ask.
- Yeah.
I'm sorry. But Jay and I are going to
Mitch and Cam's for dinner tonight.
I'm just thinking
out loud here.
What if I get a chaperone that my parents approve of?
Would it be okay then?
Well, I guess so.
You know, it would be good
for Manny to have a little bit of fun.
Do you mind if he stays here
for the party?
Mind? The plan
depended on him.
I don't suppose you've
thought of a chaperone.
Of course not, Mom, because
it's going to be a wild party,
and I'm trying to get away
with something, as usual.
Yes, I've thought of a chaperone- my
uncle, who already said he would do it.
But if that's going to be a problem,
I should just call everybody-
Sorry, sorry, sorry. It's fine.
And thank you, Uncle Manny.
Can you help a little bit?
if I push down, does that-
Yeah, that's helpin'. That's helpin',
but- it's not helping. It's stuck.
I can't believe
I've got 'em this stuck.
I built beds my whole life.
Bunk beds, dog beds, cow beds.
I'm calling you on cow beds.
Oh, that's my dad!
Oh. Okay, he can help.
He's built a boat,
a dock, a lake.
Ah, he did not build a lake. Okay, from now
on, just stop after you say the second thing.
So the cabin door swings open. Damned
if there wasn't a lady pilot in there.
Yeah, well, I hate to admit
it, but it throws me too.
I do prefer a man. Are we gonna
have this conversation again?
Hey, Merle.
Hey. How are you?
Okay. Let me grab that for you.
No, no, I got it.
I will take that beer
you were about to offer me though.
Oh, yeah, coming right up. And you know
where everything is. Go have a seat.
Oh, I missed a call
from my dad.
Oh, let me guess.
Is he calling to cancel?
What's his excuse this time?
You know, that's a really
mean thing to assume, Cam.
I really wish you'd give
my dad a break for once.
Oh, please. You know Jay
doesn't like my dad.
He thinks he's some bumpkin
from the sticks.
Well, I will have you know that Merle Stonewall
Tucker is one of the most respected farmers ...
in all of Hell's Hollow, Missouri.
Okay, you're not
hearing yourself.
- My dad likes him just fine.
- Come on.
Hello.
Hey, Dad, it's me.
Mitch.
I'm sick.
I gotta cancel tonight.
Yeah. Yeah, at 6:00. We're
really lookin' forward to it.
What are you doing?
I said I can't come.
I don't know. Let me ask. My dad
wants to know red or white.
Um, uh, red.
Red.
And I'm sorry.
Okay. Yeah,
Cam says red.
Okay.
Yeah, he-he's so happy-
Knock it off, old man! You are not sick.
Why do you always do this?
Okay, look. Between you and
me, Mervis kind of bugs me.
First of all, it's Merle. Mervis isn't a name.
Mervis is a sound.
And second of all, he's my partner's
father, okay? You're coming.
Okay, Dad,
why don't you settle in?
We don't have any plans until
dinner tonight with Jay and Gloria.
- I don't like that guy.
- What? That's- You like everybody.
Not Jay.
Guy rubs me the wrong way.
Every time I try to do somethin' nice,
he makes this cranky face, like-
Okay. Well, you know what?
I'm gonna chalk this up to jet lag for you,
because it's not like you at all, okay?
You have to make an effort.
it's my partner's father.
Now, give me the growl
that means okay.
Good.
Did you know Walt had a daughter
he was completely estranged from?
His lawyer said she wouldn't even honor his
last request to toss his dog tags in the ocean.
Can you imagine? Phil, do we really
have to go through this again?
I told you I would do
everything possible ...
to make sure that your skeleton ends up
in a science class at a women's college.
No, it's just sad.
That's half of what will
keep me going in my old age.
Remembering all the good
times with the kids. Oh.
Teaching Luke
to ride his bike.
Haley at
the father-daughter dance.
Taking Alex for
her first pony ride.
You never took Alex
on a pony ride.
Oh, right, that was just me.
Mm-hmm.
But Alex and I went, um-
Oh, no, that was Haley.
Mmm.
Huh.
Phil. Look, it's Luke.
He's going into WaIt's house.
Aw.
He's saying good-bye.
He just needed
a little time.
That is so sweet
and so sad. Wow.
He's so much more sensitive
than I ever thought.
They had a special bond.
I wouldn't be surprised if one day he
wrote a book like Tuesdays With Morrie.
I never read it.
Did that guy steal Morrie's TV?
Now setting a course
for adventure.
# Beep-boop-beep-bop
boop-boop-boop #
I've had great experiences
with all my kids, but I-
I might have fallen
behind a bit with Alex.
My fault completely.
Adventure? We are throwing dog tags
into an already polluted ocean ...
where they will probably
choke an otter.
Eighty percent my fault.
Honey, we're bringing closure
to a man's life.
We'll hike up to
the scenic overlook-
where apparently Walt
proposed to his wife-
wait for the light to be just right,
say a few words, share some memories.
It's kind of poetic.
Kind of Navaho.
Now you're getting it.
We'll be sending him off with a level
of dignity that, if we're lucky,
some day we'll experience too.
It's called-
Huh.
Hey, what have you got there?
WaIt's old TV?
He said that I could take
one thing after he died.
I wish he would
have said two things.
I would have taken that phone
with the big buttons.
I bet you guys had some really good
times watching this thing, right?
No. I just wanted
a TV in my room.
You know, Luke, there might be a
nicer way to honor WaIt's memory.
- What do you mean?
- Well, I mean, you guys liked to garden.
We could, uh- We could take one of his
flowers and plant it in our yard.
And then every spring, when-
Ah, there we go.
Sweetie, how you feeling?
Are you sad? Angry?
Confused? Frustrated?
You know, you can talk to me.
I know, but I can't see through you.
Could you scooch?
No, no. You know, this is not okay.
it's going back.
What? He said I could pick one thing.
This isn't picking.
It's looting,
and it's going back.
Oh! You are so mean.
When Walt used to look through
those binoculars ...
and say, "Your dad's one
lucky man," he was wrong.
Hi, Haley. Hi. Stef,
Sam, this is Manny.
What's up, dude? Kitchen's over
there and pool's in the back.
So where are your parents?
They're not coming.
I was told there'd be a chaperone.
There is. It's you.
My parents are totally
fine with it.
Well, exits, fire
extinguisher, burn kit.
Okay, let's have some fun.
Y;  I believe it was
clear the bedrooms are off-limits.
Young lady, I don't think you're ready up
here for what you're planning to do up there.
Not on my watch.
Oh, this was
a delicious meal, Mitchell.
I wish my wife could cook
a roast like this.
You got a good 'un there, Son.
Well, I'm very lucky.
never had a bad patch.
Except the winter of '85.
Remember that?
Oh, I spent several nights
in the cow bed then. Hmm.
Oh, here. Let me help you. No, no, no.
You sit- sit down.
Let's us guys catch up
here a little bit. Yeah.
I'll tell you why I don't like that guy,
and I could never say this to Mitch.
He treats my son like the wife
in the relationship. Always has.
Before we get to dessert,
I've got some presents here.
- Oh, you didn't need to, Dad.
- Ay-
Love it.
Oh, Merle,
thank you so much.
Look at this.
Oh, so elegant, huh?
Oh, this is so sweet.
I think I might cry.
Don't.
Dad, I've really
gotta get home-
I know, I know,
you gotta do homework.
You can't expect me to see a sign that says
"World's Greatest Milk Shake, 50 Miles" ...
and not drive to it.
Sorry, sweetie.
Machine's broken.
Huh.
I just wanted a special day
with my daughter, you know?
Like the time we gave an old man a
dramatic send-off at the beach.
Or-Or the time we drove a hundred miles
for the world's greatest milk shake.
Call us when it
happens, Francine.
Oh, could be
before you get home.
I'm a week past
my due date as it is.
What can I do for you?
The time
we delivered a baby.
We were the only ones there,
and she was so close.
The sound of a pin dropping
could induce labor.
Okay.
What looks good?
Well, uh-
Barn!
Whoa!
- Kids love to destroy things.
- Not Manny.
He's always been
a little bit too serious.
I would make the buildings,
and he will inspect them,
and if they weren't up to code-
ay, ay, ay, the paperwork.
I remember Cam one time rolled a
tractor tire right through a chicken coop.
He was three at the time.
Huh. Yeah, I remember Mitchell one time
karate chopped a plate glass window.
Got 17 stitches.
Ay, yes, I love that story.
Which one of the Charlie's
Angels he was being again?
It's not important.
I think it was Farrah.
Yeah, the thing I remember
is when Mitchell told that story,
how he giggled all the way through it.
I'm sure he wasn't giggling.
Oh, yeah, he-he was giggling, all right.
No, see, Mitchell
has a booming laugh.
It's Cameron, actually,
has the high laugh.
You know-
No, I believe Mitch has a higher
laugh than-
No, it's-
Listen to them.
- Listen to them. Best of friends.
- Oh, man.
I'm sorry I doubted Jay.
He's been lovely.
Oh, well, confession time.
He kind of didn't want to come.
Oh.
Well, you're gonna laugh, because my
dad was kind of hoping he wouldn't.
Wha-
They just needed to get to know one another better.
I am so glad that we did this.
Yeah, me too.
Oh.
That's so funny. What did your dad not
like about my dad? Oh, well, you know Jay.
He's a teddy bear, but sometimes he
can kind of come off as a tough guy.
Yeah, that's true.
As an actual tough guy, you can kind of see
how that would rub my dad the wrong way.
Oh, that's-
I-l could see that.
But, you know, my dad's actually
pretty tough himself, so-
Oh, yeah. City tough.
You know, not farm tough.
Uh-huh. You mean, cities,
where there are gangs,
as opposed to farms,
where there are ducks?
Boy, that's really
jammed in there.
Yep. Why don't you
hop on in there, Dad?
- My dad's got it.
- All right, let's see here. Hang on, Merle.
Here.  That's good.
It's comin'.
- We got it. We got it.
- Oh, there you go.
Cam, why don't you go get us
a couple of cold ones?
We'll finish
this job up in here.
Sure thing, Dad.
You earned it.
Yeah. Good helpin' there,
Merle. Okay.
Wow. It's hot in here.
It's like 80 degrees.
He did that so the Meals On Wheels
lady had to take off her sweater.
How do we turn on
the lights in here?
Of course.
So, Luke. Now that we're here, you want to
take a minute and say what Walt meant to you?
Nope.
Luke, you are going through
something huge in your life,
and I'm concerned that you're not
processing it in a normal, healthy way.
I'm sad.
I'm so very sad.
No, I don't just want to hear what you think
I want to hear. I want you to really-
Hi. it's Kim
with Meals on Wheels.
Oh. Hi, Luke. Where's Walt?
It is like a sauna in here. How does he stand it?
Walt! I'm waiting for my hug!
I have some sad news
about Walt.
He's dead.
What?
- He died last night.
- Are you joking?
No.
He had a heart attack.
A man died.
You're-You're smiling.
I'm not smiling. You are, Mom.
It's kinda creepy.
Hello! Walt?
What's goin' on?
Something happen to Walt?
Mm-hmm.
- Well, I'm sure you can imagine.
- He's sick?
He's in the hospital?
Oh, my God. Just tell me.
Okay. He is dead.
- He is?
- Yeah, he's dead.
What are you doin'
with your mouth?
Nothing.  She's smiling.
She thinks it's funny.
I don't.
I don't think it's funny.
I'm not-
I'm not leaving this with you.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry. I just found
out my face does this.
Wow, Mom,
that was so wrong.
Well, it's-it's called
a coping mechanism, Luke.
Some people repress their feelings,
and some people just smile.
It- It doesn't matter. Just put the TV in the den.
Let's get out of here.
It doesn't go in the den.
It goes right here.
I can see it from my room.
Sometimes I'd wake up in the middle
of the night and look down here.
If the TV was on,
I knew he was up.
I don't know.
I guess I'm gonna miss that.
Yeah, that's-
Yeah.
Oh.
Is that any better?
Yeah.
It still feels just,
you know, a little wobbly.
Oh! Oh, my God.
Okay, no, no, no.
That's-That's fine.
Thank you. Thank you.
Ohh!
Okay. it's go time.
Oh. Hey, Doc.
Huh. That's okay.
It's just a cramp.
Can I get you guys
anything else?
Please, no. He's already made me eat the
world's greatest everything on the menu.
Dad, why are you
acting like this?
Is this about Walt dying?
No. it's about what he didn't do
when he was alive-
have a special bond
with his daughter.
I don't want to be that kind of dad.
I want to be Eugene Cernan.
Who's Eugene Cernan? Apollo 17 astronaut.
Last man on the moon.
Coolest dad of all time.
When he was leaving the moon,
he reached down and wrote his daughter's
initials into the lunar surface.
Since there's no atmosphere-
They'll be there forever.
Wow. So every time she looks in the sky,
she knows there's a message just for her.
Exactly. That's why dads
everywhere hate Eugene Cernan.
Oh, no.
Okay, hate's a strong word.
it's just I'm trying to make-
Oh. Oh, boy.
Honey. Okay.
I really want to help, but you know
when someone yawns, it makes you yawn?
You're not gonna yawn,
are you?
I already yawned
a little in my mouth.
Jay, I want to thank you
for helping me do this.
I know Cam appreciates
not having to do it all on his own.
What?
What's that face?
You really want to know?
Sure.
Sometimes I think you treat my son
like the woman in their relationship.
- What?
- Like those watches.
Cam's was all big and manly.
The other one looked like
something Grace Kelly would wear.
Well, that's just because Mitch has a more
slender wrist than Cam does. That's all.
It's skinny, not slender.
And you're honestly tellin' me you don't
cast Mitch in the more ladylike role?
Are you sayin' Cam is
the wife in this deal?
I don't think about it that way.
it's not like it was in our day.
Husband went out to work.
Wife stayed home with the kids.
That sounds like
a clever way of saying yes.
Fine.
They're both equal.
Neither one is the wife.
Yeah, yeah.
I know that in my head.
It's just that it makes me
feel a tiny bit better ...
to think that the person he's spending
his life with is a tiny bit of a woman.
I get it.
Every time I start to feel
comfortable with this thing,
some new part comes up
I gotta wrap my head around.
Yeah. I guess we got no choice.
Yep.
We got two sons, and they're
gay for each other. Hmm.
I'll take it slow
on the way home.
Don't worry. Canceling
course for adventure.
# Beep-boop-beep-bap-boop #
You know what
I'll never forget?
The time my dad spent an entire day
trying to create a special memory for me.
Or when a pregnant lady
slipped in my vomit.
Hang on.
I want to do one thing
before we go.
Hey.
You on your way home?
Just about.
How's everything there?
Actually, it's pretty great.
I can't wait to see you.
Me too.
Okay.
Let's hit it.
I don't know.
Feel like maybe we should get
some food on the way home.
Don't.
Maybe a nice tuna melt.
Stop it.
I did what I could, Mom.
It was a nightmare. I can't tell you how
many times I turned off the bathroom light.
Haley!
Oh, crap. Listen, Gloria.
Okay. Everything I told you
technically was not-
You lied to me so that you could
have a party without supervision!
Oh, I had plenty
of supervision.
He was running around all night
with his coasters and vacuum ...
and his
"make good choices" speech.
Good. Somebody needed to be responsible.
Thank you.
Not you. You take rules
too seriously.
- I'm in trouble?
- You are 13.
You're not supposed to be
vacuuming the party.
You're supposed to be
enjoying the party. Exactly.
A party that you
shouldn't have been having!
Seems like you're
sending mixed signals here.
Yeah. Maybe I should get
my friends and leave-
No, you're in trouble, little young lady.
You're having this party.
What? They've been using
glassware by the pool,
putting feet on the furniture and
begging girls to kiss each other.
Yes. All the things that
you should have been doing!
Yeah, all those things are fine.
Go. Have fun and go crazy!
But he's gonna
ruin my party.
Two birds with one bullet.
English - US - PSDH