Oh, thank you so much for the donation.
I wish I could do more.
It's just a bunch of old, out-of-date clothes.
Oh, I'm sure it's great.
Three weeks ago,
our neighbors, the Rands,
lost their house and
everything they own in a fire.
Fortunately,
nobody was hurt.
And fortunately, they're friends
with Wonder Woman over here.
I'm hardly Wonder Woman.
She mobilized the community to donate
clothes, furniture, appliances.
All to help them start over in their
new rental- Which you found them.
I'm no Wonder Woman.
Rand-Aid was her idea.
Wasn't my idea
to call it Rand-Aid.
Okay, fine.
I'm Wonder Woman.
Terrible tragedy.
They're our closest friends.
We know them. Uh, Manny and
their son Reuben are tight.
In fact, I put in one of their closets.
Not that it matters, but it was
the only structure to survive the fire.
Par favor,
don't even say that word.
In my country, it is considered
very, very bad luck...
when your house burns down.
Th-They lived
a block away from us.
Smoke was everywhere. I was so
upset, I couldn't sleep for days.
Of course, Mitchell
won't let me take anything.
Well, Cam, we both know why.
Some people have been known to sleepwalk
or even sleep-drive on that medication.
Cam's reaction is much worse.
Oh! No!
Oh, God! Oh, God.
I sleep-clown.
- Dad, you're gonna kill yourself.
- I got it.
We're on a schedule here.
I still have to pick up the truck.
If you want him to
stop lifting things,
put all this in grocery bags
and turn the TV on to a football game.
Oh, take this phone
away from me.
Why?
Two of our best brokers left
to start their own agency,
and the office gossip is flying.
But I want today to be about the Rands,
and if I have this-
Oh, my God. Those guys took two
secretaries and the tube dude with them.
Who's the tube dude?
You know, the blowy guy that attracts
all the attention. This guy.
Ah, sí, I've seen him.
He goes down with the air,
and then he shakes up.
He goes down in the air, and then
up- You almost got it. Yeah.
- And then goes down.
- Hi, hi. Sorry.
We would've been here sooner, but
this one had a wardrobe crisis.
You know, it's a somber occasion,
and all my tops are too joyful.
- You do not want our problems.
- No.
Here, Jay, let me- No, I got it.
Dad! Ah! My back'
No, Jay,
that's not quite it.
Remember, you got air blowin' through you.
So it's more like-
And then out and then out.
# Hey, hey #
# Hey ##
Leave me alone.
I'm fine.
I've gotta pick up that truck.
- I'd be happy to get the truck.
- I don't think so. it's a pretty big truck.
Oh. Is it- Is it bigger than the combine
I've been driving since I was 12 years old?
Or the windrow tractor
with MacDon header...
that I drove to and parallel parked
at my high school prom?
Hmm?
At least something
got plowed that night.
Heard that.
- Son of a bitch!
- Your low back is in spasm, Jay.
I can massage that
out for you.
I'm fine. Dad, you don't
know what you're missing.
Phil is a magician.
And a licensed masseur.
Before I heard the siren song of residential
real estate, I was bitten by the rub bug.
No, he's-he's amazing.
I had this knot in my leg.
Two minutes with Phil,
and it was gone.
I'm sorry, but I think you might
have a higher tolerance...
for a man's hands
on your body than I do.
Charming.
Ay, don't be an idiot.
Let Phil help you.
- Fine.
- Great! I'll just go get the room ready.
You'll be surprised
with what these hands can do.
Really? Can they drive a Bobcat
skid-steer with a bucket grapple...
through a school hallway
on a dare?
Because these can, and have.
Poor Reuben, huh?
Having to rebuild
his whole life at age 12.
Yeah. That blows.
I know we're both shaken up,
but let's watch the language.
Okay, put this in a safe place.
it's for Reuben.
It's one of those, um, how do you say again?
Is that the helicopter with the camera
in it that you control with your phone?
The one I asked for?
Okay, when your house burn down,
you get one of these.
No, don't burn your house down.
How lucky is Reuben?
So lucky.
You know what? I say we take this
thing out and see how she flies.
I don't know.
My morn got it for Reuben.
Oh, so now he won't even share his toys?
He never does.
Screw that guy!
Yeah!
You're a terrible influence.
You need me.
Claire, in case
you want to add something,
I put the box of dresses outside, and
this is the box of snicker-snackers.
Mmm.
Thanks.
Mitchell, we did have something
to add to this box of, um,
snicker-snackers.
- What?
- English is not her first language.
- She's just trying to help.
- Mitchell, come on. You can't do that.
You can't just change the rules.
it's what we do.
When Gloria says something silly,
we innocently laugh behind her back.
Come on. She's had a
rough week, all right?
She's really worried about tia
Maria Cecilia and that surgery.
Oh, and then she lost
her cell phone at Pilates.
- How do you know this?
- We have coffee.
Oh, "have." So when did
this become, like, a thing?
What's the big deal? We're friends.
I like Gloria.
Uh, it's no big deal. It's-
I have nothing against her.
I just think- Oh!
All right. So before you get all
judgey, I gave her that vase.
After I gave it to you.
You couldn't part
with that T-shirt?
I love this shirt.
You know, you don't have
to look the way you look.
Amber Rand lost all her clothes in a fire, but
she gets to build herself a new wardrobe.
Let me burn your clothes.
Girls, get down here!
There's a lot of work to do!
She's in a mood. You
know what we have to do, right?
There's no way you're my real sister!
I hate you!
I can't believe- You're the
most selfish, shallow-
That's it! I cannot take the fighting!
Just get out of the house.
Works every time.
You know, I don't even want to drive the truck
anymore, even though on the farm I was-
I can't take
another farm story.
Yay! You might want to
take someone with you.
The thing's been parked there
six months.
You're gonna want to
hose it down, sweep for spiders.
Good news, girls.
You're goin' with Uncle Cam.
Huh?
The pain must've
been pretty bad...
if I was asking Phil for help.
His need for my approval
is exhausting.
In 10 years, I've asked him for one
thing- to hook up my wireless printer.
He still won't shut up about it.
How's that
printer workin' out for you?
Still lovin' that printer, huh?
If your printer breaks from
here, I can fix it on my phone.
Can you? I can, but I don't need
to, because I fixed it forever.
Just once, I wish he wouldn't make
such a big deal about everything.
Okay. Now just disrobe and place
the towel over your buttocks.
Ridin' the open
road in a big rig like this...
sure can work up
a man's powerful appetite.
We've gone five blocks.
Do you want a
burger or not? I could eat.
Hey, Alex, maybe Uncle Cam will
let you borrow his hat later.
You know, since you dress like a dude.
I like the way I dress.
Uncle Cam, as her future prom date, will
you please talk to her? You know fashion.
First of all, you're each
beautiful in your own way.
But you're both playing for second,
because I'm too sexy for this truck.
I have to say, you do drive it surprisingly well.
Yeah, who'd have thought?
Surprising?
What, that-that a gay man
can drive a truck?
You know, I expect that kind of
thinking from Jay's generation.
But from our future generation?
No.
Wow. This place got crowded.
Oh. You're
really wedged in there.
You want us to help
guide you out?
That question?
It was like a hate crime.
Sorry!
- Hey, you're really close on this side.
- Yeah, I see it.
- Careful!
- I'm being careful.
Gasping? Really?
Holding hands.
We're not in a nosedive.
Look, if it would make you
feel better, get out and guide me.
Okay, come on.
Let's go.
Please don't yell at me,
but there's not enough room.
Okay, climb over.
You're fine.
You know, the Native Americans believed
that burning sage kept bad energy away.
How'd that work out for 'em?
Get to the back.
That's the spirit.
Thank you.
Now I just need to make sure
that the oil is a perfect 98.6.
And it is perfect.
Now, I want you to take
a deep breath,
and let me transport you
to a land I call Relaxistan.
Oh, what the hell?
Get off me!
I knew this was a terrible-
Oh, Mama Lucian,
that's good.
Shh.
So you want to try it?
Uh, I don't know.
I'm still feeling guilty.
It's Reuben's helicopter.
Reuben is the whole reason
we should be doing this.
He's barely-living proof that
life can change in a second.
You gotta grab what you can
when you can.
What is this hold
you have on me?
Wow.
- Okay, now ease up.
- Okay, I'm easing up.
- Okay, it's not working.
- Get ahold of yourself, Manny! She's getting away!
- I can't hold her!
- Give it to me! Mayday! Mayday!
Oh, well. What do you mean, "Oh, well"?
My mom's gonna kill us.
Us?
You were flying it.
I was in the attic,
packing boxes.
You're gonna help me find it, or
the next search will be for you.
I like this guy.
Where's he been?
Just relax.
Let me know
if I'm hurting you.
Are you kidding me?
it's fantastic.
I love you.
This.
I love this.
It just slipped out. Those are the
worst three words I could say to Phil.
I was just praying he would let it
go and not make a big deal about it.
Oh, my God.
This is huge.
Jay, I'm sorry.
I need a minute.
Son of a bitch!
Son of a bitch.
Oh, these are fantastic. Why
is Manny getting rid of 'em?
He said that
they were last season.
I used to have a pair like these.
I can never find 'em anymore.
Oh, there's an outlet store.
They don't have men's size, but I'm sure the
biggest size for boys will fit you perfectly.
- I'll take you.
- All right, it's a date.
Oh. Another date.
Claire, I heard what
happened with the vase,
but I don't want you
to worry about it.
I'm so sorry. I should've
told you about that sooner.
I just- I have really been
shaken by this whole fire thing.
You know,
life is... so fragile.
I know.
Like a vase.
You tattled on me?
She asked me about it.
What was I supposed to do?
Why are you making those cruel
sounds with your mouth?
You don't see it? You're
turning Gloria into Mom.
What?
Mm-hmm.
First, you got
all defensive of her,
and then
you tattled on me to her.
That's exactly what you did with old Mom.
It's what you're doing with new Mom.
Okay, okay. Only you could make my
friendship with Gloria into something ugly.
Don't get me wrong.
I think it's sweet.
We've all got our thing.
You have mommy issues.
I do not have mommy issues.
Okay, so I pick you up
tomorrow.
We go get you
your big boy pants,
and then we go and get
a little ice cream, okay?
Perfect.
I don't want to hear it.
Ay. You still
don't feel very good?
I told Phil I loved him.
Oh- it was an accident, but you
know how he gets with that stuff.
Ay, I know.
Jay, can I talk to you later
about what just happened?
Yeah.
Thanks.
Geez,
I just worked that out.
You're screwed.
Today is the biggest day
of my life.
Just relax.
Let me know
if I'm hurting you.
Are you kidding me?
it's fantastic.
I love you.
This.
I love this.
Oh, my God.
This is huge.
Jay, I'm sorry.
I need a minute.
The two guys
who left the firm...
asked me to quit my job and partner
with them at the new agency.
Big opportunity,
big risk.
And they need an answer
by the end of the day.
I don't always make great
decisions under pressure.
What the hell is that?
An alpaca.
I got the last one!
Come on, man! Move that truck!
I hate you!
Okay, so I flirted with a table of
truckers who have offered to help us.
No! No help!
I've come too far.
Have you?
Hey, they don't sell pizzas at this restaurant!
You parked here illegally.
Congratulations, sir.
You're destroying America.
Hey, there are no cars behind us.
Go. Gun it!
- on! on!
- All right! Okay!
All right, everybody, relax!
We're fine! We're fine!
We are not fine!
And we're all smushed!
And we're scared! And we're
tilted at a 30 degree angle!
Nerd! And we're dirty
and tired and late!
Okay, can
you please just be quiet?
Why couldn't we have just
asked for help?
'Cause I'm teaching you girls
a very valuable lesson-
that gay men can do anything
straight men can do.
Yeah, we know that. Do you think
you're the only gay guy that we know?
Yeah. My soccer coach is gay.
Our pediatrician.
My Latin tutor. Nerd!
Our electrician.
Then why were you so surprised
when I said I could drive a truck?
Not because you're gay, because you're you.
And by the way, you can't.
Okay, wow. I guess I
owe you an apology.
I made a leap there. I'm just
used to dealing with stereotypes.
I'm a little sensitive
about it.
Oh. Hey, there's that trucker
that I talked to. Hey!
Excuse me. Hi! Could you
give us a hand, please?
Sure thing, sweetie.
Oh, like she'll
be able to help us.
Oh, boy, do you have
the right idea.
I could use a little break from the mother
and child reunion going on down there.
Don't ask.
Mitchell's turning Gloria into Mom.
Barn! it's out. Hmm.
You remember the way Mom
and Mitchell used to be...
in their private little club?
Just the two of them,
no one else allowed in.
Well-
it's happening again.
But this time around,
it's happening with your wife.
You should see them down there.
It'd actually be adorable
if it weren't so sick.
I just-
You know, I feel like Mitchell
is a grown man, he has a child,
and he's still working out some
psychodrama from 20 years ago.
Daddy, can I have a sip of your beer?
Thanks.
Oh, my God.
Mitchell cozies up to Morn.
I go running to Daddy.
I'm the one
who's turning Gloria into Morn,
which is really disturbing,
since we're the same age.
You're older.
Oh.
Oh, that's where
we're gonna chime in.
Will you hurry up?
I'm saving my strength,
'cause if we don't find this
helicopter, I'm walking to Canada.
Hope you like taxes.
Hey, that's our helicopter!
Is it, now? I'm sure you have the
proper documentation for that.
Just give it back.
it's ours.
You guys are bullies. They can't be bullies.
They're nerds.
Don't pigeonhole us.
We can be both.
Oh.
ls there an issue here?
Uncle Cam,
I got this.
Oh, my God, it's Alex Dunphy.
So awesome.
What's the problem here, boys?
These geeks won't give us back our
helicopter that we took from Reuben.
Is that right,
Abraham?
Oh, my God,
she knows your name.
Helicopter, please.
I love you.
What just happened?
You have your fans,
I have mine.
Someday, your fans are
going to work for my fans.
Oh. Um, Gloria, do you mind if I
talk to Mitchell alone for a minute?
It's okay. I already know what you
said, and I think it's crazy.
Mitchell is not making me
his mommy.
No, I know, he's not.
But I think that I might be.
Okay, now you're going really, really
crazy, because I am younger than you.
Mmm, by 14 months,
so let's settle down.
What is going
on with you today?
I- All right,
I'm working this out as I go.
I think maybe seeing you get all
buddy-buddy today with Gloria...
made me feel like it did
when you were with Morn.
And-And- I don't know,
I-l felt like the odd man out.
Okay. Well, that's how I used
to feel with you and Dad.
I know.
I know. We-We chose teams,
even during the divorce, and-
Okay, the last couple of years, you and
I have been our own team, you know?
And I don't want that
to go away.
So, I guess I just felt a
little left out today. Shutup.
Okay, can you two
try hugging a box...
so that your poor mother doesn't
have to do all the hard work?
I am sorry, Gloria,
about all the mom stuff today.
I just- I got this crazy idea that
you like Mitchell better than me.
I do like Mitchell
better than you.
Why?
Ay, please.
Are you going to
honestly tell me...
that I'm your favorite
person in this family?
I'm not even your favorite
Colombian in this family.
I would love to get closer to you.
You have my number.
But call me quickly,
because I book up.
You never saw me!
There you are. I really
need to talk to you.
You really don't. Jay, please.
it's about work.
I got a text
during your massage.
I've been offered a
partnership in a new agency.
Oh.
Good for you.
Well, I'm not so sure.
I mean, there's-there's a big upside,
but I have a stable job right now.
I have three kids, and at least
one of 'em's going to college.
Worst-case scenario,
they all go.
Well, what does Claire think?
I haven't told her yet. I
wanted to talk to you first.
You've done this.
Well, I think that there's
only really one question.
Whether I'm ready
to run my own company?
Nah, you're great with people.
We know you're a good salesman.
You've managed to provide
a good living in tough times.
Then what?
Is this the right time?
Never a perfect time.
House could burn down tomorrow.
Question is, do you want this?
Yeah.
Yeah, I really want it.
Then gamble on yourself.
I'd gamble on you.
I'm gonna do it.
There you go.
Thanks, Jay.
Hey, look, I know you were
reluctant to get that massage,
but I think we can both agree
it had a happy ending.
Please don't say that.
If I could only save
one possession in a fire-
Probably my first set of golf clubs.
My old man gave 'em to me.
Here, I got it.
No,no,no.
The engagement ring that
Jay gave me that changed my life.
Lily's adoption papers.
I Was gonna
say adoption papers.
So I guess then I would say
my mama's recipe book.
All our family photos...
which I keep on my iPad,
so my iPad.
As long as I had my family,
I wouldn't need anything else.
What?
You say somethin' like that,
it makes us all seem petty.
Yeah. I know. I know.
Boo!
Hiss!
Shh. Cam's sleeping.
I don't want to wake him.
He's had a rough day.
Not as rough
as Grandpa's truck.
Shh.
Thank you so much for driving
me.
I really didn't want to ride
in that big rig.
It was amazing.
Everybody was honking, and I
learned, like, five new curse words.
Mostly from Cam.
Shh!
I'm glad
I could give you a laugh today.
I didn't know that's what I was
to you people, a big joke.
No, honey, it wasn't like that.
No, we didn't mean-
- Uncle Cam, we love you.
- Save it.
I'm going back to bed.
So he's still doing that?
Yeah, yeah. But we're
workin' on it.
English - US - PSDH