Councilwoman Dunphy,
how do you respond to allegations ...
that you look super sexy
in your new suit?
I haven't been
elected yet.
Come on, kids!
We gotta vote!
Honey, come on. Please stop filming.
I'm just excited.
After today, you are
going to be a Councilwoman,
and I am going to be
a first husband.
Well, if you don't stop filming,
you're going to be my first husband.
All right, everybody,
come on!
You know what you're doing, kids?
You guys are manning the phone banks.
Alex, you're in charge of that.
What? Why is she in charge? And
wh-what's a phone bank? That's why.
Phil?
I got it.
I will be driving 50 of our finest
senior citizens to the polls,
assuming, of course, that they
remember that I'm coming for them.
Redirect.
High five.
- Old people occasionally forget things.
- Okay.
All right, everybody, let's go. Wait, wait.
Real quick. Sorry.
Everybody get in there.
Jump in there.
I just want to say how
proud of you we all are.
You're an inspiration.
Who would've thought that 20 years ago, when
you were still in the bloom of your youth-
Okay, I'm gonna
go start the car.
Claire likes to win.
When she was eight,
a little Girl Scout friend of hers ...
bragged she could
sell the most cookies.
Damned if Claire didn't
walk the neighborhood ...
till she got blisters
on her feet,
and won by 10 boxes.
Best part is, Claire
wasn't even a Girl Scout.
The choice is Claire.
Vote Claire Dunphy
for town council!
What?  Oh, I love it!
- What do you think, huh?
- I love it.
We got it on Craigslist.
- Came off a taco truck.
- It did.
I love that you're doing this for me.
Thank you!
You 're welcome!
I know how important
winning is to Claire.
And I love to festoon things.
We're her dream team.
So we cleared the whole day, dropped Lily
off at school and voted first thing.
Although one of us had a bit
of a dimpled chad situation.
Can you tell me how this
machine works again, Chad?
Oh, sure,
no problem.
Just vote over here. Just-
# Hey, hey #
# Hey ##
Thank you.
I can see Claire-ly now
that Duane is gone!
Bye! Thank you!
Oh, my gosh. Okay, everybody, get in the car.
Let's go, let's go.
Good luck today, Claire.
Oh, Laurie, thank you.
By the way, we have
some really good news.
What's that? Becky got into
the University of Oregon.
Oh, congratulations.
Any news, Haley?
Uh, no, not- not yet.
But, you know,
super psyched!
This whole waiting to hear thing ...
has been a nightmare
since the very first letter.
I'm too nervous.
I can't do it.
"Dear Ms. Dunphy,
we regret
to inform you-"
What?
Don't leave me hanging.
After that, I decided to only
tell my parents good news.
I have one school left.
The only good news
I've gotten is that ...
my annoying neighbor Becky
is moving back east to Oregon.
Manny, write this down.
I didn't bring a pen.
Election day
is America at its finest.
The people speak
and the government listens.
I don't know
what they do in Colombia.
No one does,
and don't ask.
I mean, we know
that voting's a privilege,
but for my daughter to have her name on
that ballot, it just means so much more-
You know what? I think I'm gonna vote later.
What? Where you going?
The line is too long.
It's only three people,
and nobody has a gun.
Eh.
We 're here! We 're Claire!
Get used to it!
Mmm. You know, I'm not sure if that's tracking.
Here, let me try one.
You don't have to be Claire-voyant
to know who to vote for!
Vote Dunphy
for town council.
Uh- Uh-
Uh, Claire Dunphy.
Uh, C-Claire's
her first name.
I'm sorry
if that wasn't Claire.
Oh, my God,
look at that.
There's a trash can
right there,
and that guy just threw
his paper on the sidewalk.
Hey, you in the yellow jacket. Pick
it up and put it in the trash.
Oh-
Sorry!
Oh, my God, he did it.
Yes, he did.
Ooh, here,
let me try one.
Hey, dragon tattoo!
No jaywalking!
Oh, my gosh, this is
an instrument of power.
How could they not sell tacos? You
know what we could do with this thing?
Cam, we could really
make a difference.
We could be
the voice of change.
Ooh, I got it.
Let's go yell at the dry cleaner
that lost my shirt.
Come on, gang.
Today is the Dunphys
at their best.
- Hi.
- Hey.
- I'm from the Weekly Saver.
Mind if I ask you a couple
questions about the big election?
Not at all.
Fire away.
Who are you
voting for today?
Claire Dunphy.
Finally. I've been waiting
for someone to say that name.
Why?
Because I am Claire Dunphy.
Oh. I'm sorry.
They moved me over from ad sales.
We take turns reporting.
How do you feel
about your chances today?
Not as good as I did a few minutes ago.
No, she feels great.
Urn, her spirits are high.
The whole family's high.
There's your headline.
Phil-
- How about a photo of all of you?
- Sure. Yes. Yes.
Mom. Mom, Mom. Tag. Oh, my goodness.
Thank you.
That would have been
a really awkward picture.
Okay.
Oh!
What is that? Is that a tooth?
Ewww!
Awesome!
How old are you?
Do it again.
- How does that even happen?
- It's a fake tooth from an old ice skating injury.
It just fell out. Oh, my gosh.
Why today?
Let's not overreact.
Let me see it.
Okay.
All right.
Oww!
Got it. Thanks.
- What happened back there?
- The line was too long. I couldn't wait.
I've seen you wait 45 minutes
in line for sherbet.
Well, I happen
to like sherbet, okay?
That place I take you has the
greatest sherbet on the West Coast.
They got lime sherbet,
they got coconut sherbet.
Why are we talking
about sherbet?
- He's clearly changing the subject.
- Why aren't you in school?
He's doing it again.
Manny's right.
You're being very ardilla.
Ardilla?
Yeah, you know.
- The- The one th-that-
- Rabbit. I was being "rabbity."
- No, the one with the cheeks and tail and-
- Chipmunk.
- Possum.
- Okay, obviously she means squirrel.
- You were being squirrelly then, you're being
squirrelly now. -Better than bein' a rat.
Manny, give us a minute.
Oh, sure.
I served him up
on a silver platter.
What?
All right,
it's no big deal.
There was a woman working there.
I didn't want her to see me.
- Who is she?
- Her name is Dottie.
- She's the first woman I dated after my divorce.
- You dated a Dottie after Dede?
You're focusing on the wrong thing here.
The point is, it ended badly.
I tried to let her down easy, but,
uh, she didn't take it too well.
Actually, I don't know how she
took it 'cause I wasn't there.
We dated a few weeks,
then after we, you know-
I slipped out of her house before she
woke up and never called her again.
Put my pants on in her yard,
put the car in neutral,
let it roll down the driveway,
lights off.
Hey, I can't talk
about this anymore.
So because of this woman, you
didn't vote for your daughter?
It's Claire.
We need her to win.
I don't want to be around when
something that tight comes unraveled.
I'll figure out something. Maybe
those poll workers take shifts.
Stop hiding in your little cave
like a- like, you know, like the-
the- the-
I really don't want to do this again.
No, th-the big one.
Like the monster furry one.
Why can't I remember any animal names?
Climb aboard
the Dunphy Express.
Next stop, democracy.
What? No, no.
Please don't go.
I won't do that anymore.
I promise.
Oh. Uh, we need to
make a quick stop.
I gotta pick up my new glasses.
No can do.
I, uh- I got a lot
of people waiting, so-
it'll just take
two minutes.
I can't even see the ballot
without my glasses.
I mark the wrong box, next thing you
know, I'll be married to a guy.
Yeah, I-l don't think
it's mandatory, Walt.
I'm a good dancer.
They'll come for me.
They will break all your buttons and
say you brought it in that way!
Okay, go, go, go!
Turns out we had
a lot of axes to grind.
And a hybrid, so there was
virtually no stopping us.
Do not see that movie.
You will neither laugh nor cry.
Best pizza in the city? Not
even the best' pizza on the street.
They do not do the hair of the
people on those pictures.
Totally ?ee checking ?
Don't bank on it.
Okay, that was really fun, but now we
gotta go back to campaigning for Claire.
We've been saying that for two hours.
Yes, but now I really mean it.
- Oh, my God, there's Sandy.
- Sandra Bullock?
Yes, Sandra Bullock. We're such
good friends, I call her Sandy, so-
No, Sandy who works at Lily's preschool.
Oh, yeah.
You know, she got engaged. No!
To the gay boyfriend?
Totally.
Oh, how
does she not see it?
If I was with somebody that gorgeous,
I'd overlook a few quirks too.
First of all, thank you.
Second of all,
point well taken.
Mmm, poor Sandy.
I feel so bad for her.
It's better than being alone.
Is it?
She's looking over here.
Oh, my God.
Mitchell you're sitting on the button.
No. No, I'm not.
No, I'm not!
It's stuck! And you're the
one that had it last,
when you were taunting the cheese shop.
Oh, please. You know what?
If you advertise truffle cheese,
there are certain expectations.
Hi, Sandy.
I'm calling on behalf
of Claire Dunphy.
Sure. Yeah. Uh-huh. Okay, whatever.
What a beautiful name.
I'm calling on behalf of Claire
Dunphy for town council.
All right,
how about this?
If you vote
for Claire Dunphy,
you won't have to pay taxes
for the rest of your life.
Vote for Claire.
Luke, what are you doing?
You can't say that.
Oh, like she'd be the first politician
to make a promise she can't keep.
Well, maybe I don't want
to talk to you either.
Maybe you are the one that is bothering me!
How do you like that, huh?
Gloria, I'm going to
have to ask you again ...
to please
stick to your script.
But everybody's saying no to me.
I don't get it.
Usually, when I ask someone
to do something, they just do it.
Maybe it's because
these people can't see you.
I don't like it. Can't you just
hook me up to some sort of camera?
Uh-huh. Thank you,
Maggie, for the vote.
Okay. Bye-DY'?-
Here's your seat.
Thank you.
Um, you have to excuse me.
I'm a little nervous. I've never
been on the radio before.
Don't worry about it.
Just think of it as a conversation.
Okay.
Here are your headphones. Volume control.
Don't get too far from the mic.
Okay. Make sure your
cell phone's off.
Oh, cell phone, right. And
you're not chewing gum, are you?
No, I'm not. I just had some
temporary dental work done.
The last thing-
Ohh!
And welcome back to A Matter Of Record.
I'm Cecil Van Gundy.
Joining us now
in studio ...
is District 43 town council
candidate Claire Dunphy.
Thank you, Cecil.
It's a pleasure
to be here.
So, you're a first-time candidate.
Tell us what got you involved.
It all started with
a, um- a stop sign.
I was concerned about safety
in our neighborhood ...
and I was not getting any
satisfaction from city hall.
What's wrong
with Mom?
Oh, this isn't good.
She sounds drunk.
That's not her drunk voice.
And tell us about some of the
other issues facing our town.
Where do you stand on the city's
sewage and sustainability initiative?
The so-called S.S.I.
One cannot really talk about ...
s-s-sewage and sustainability ...
without first discussing recycling.
This city can do more with its recycling program.
What the hell's wrong with her?
- She sounds drunk.
- It's a tooth thing.
Uh-oh.
What's wrong? I'm almost out of air.
Oh, boy.
- Is it serious?
- ls oxygen serious?
You know what? I lost a ton
of time getting your glasses.
I'm gonna drop you at home. You can get
your air, I can drive other people.
I don't have
any more tanks at home.
Why? That seems like
bad planning.
Well, I forgot
to order them.
My pills
make me forget things.
Oh, shoot!
I gotta take my pill!
Please tell me you have it with you.
Of course I do.
But I have to take it
with food. Don't I?
Are you asking me? Uh, yes.
I do take them with food.
I don't feel so well.
Okay, I'll get you
whatever you want.
I'll get you the air!
I'll get you the food!
Then I'll vote for
your drunk wife.
That is not
her drunk voice!
Thank you so much
for voting.
Thanks so much.
We appreciate it.
Hi. I'm terribly sorry. Excuse me.
Jay Pritchett.
Uh, can I get in and out really quick?
Thank you.
Wait, no. You have- Sir! This is all I need.
Thank you very much.
All right.
Claire, Claire, Claire.
Claire, Claire-
Aha! Here!
Oh!
- Hey!
- Oh! I'm sorry! I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Hello, Dottie!
Jay!
It's so nice to see you.
Is it? Oh, why wouldn't it be?
Well-
Oh.
That was a long time ago. Water
under the bridge. We're good.
- Oh, that's great.
- Thank you so much for voting.
You remember
my daughter, Claire.
She's- She's running
for town council.
Oh, isn't that neat?
Yeah, so proud.
So, you're gonna
put it in there, huh?
Oh, yeah, of course. Definitely.
'Cause every vote counts,
you know.
Thank you so much
for voting.
Yeah.
Boy, I'd sure
like to see ...
the sweet sight
of my vote counting.
Why would I say I'd do
something and not do it?
That would make me a liar,
instead of a trusting
widow who fell asleep ...
in the warm embrace of a man
who promised to make breakfast.
Okay, there it is.
Look, I'm so sorry.
You were the first woman I'd been
with besides my ex in 35 years.
I panicked.
A-A-And it wasn't 'cause you weren't
pretty naked or anything like that.
I'd have run
from Angie Dickinson.
Lucky her.
Dottie-
Good-bye, Jay.
Dottie, Dottie.
Please. I'm just tryin'
to get my ballot in the box.
Oh, yeah!
That sounds familiar.
You don't have to do anything.
Just let me put it in.
Shouldn't have said that.
We are so sorry.
We did not mean for you
to hear any of that.
Yes. And we shouldn't have been
gossiping in the first place.
What if you're right?
What if Gregory is gay?
When my mom said it, I didn't believe her.
She lives in Iowa.
But coming from you two- Means nothing.
We barely know your fiancé.
If he says he's straight,
he's straight.
We're getting married in a month.
People are flying in.
He signed us up for dance
classes- Oh, my God.
No. No, no, no.
Hey.
This is what gays do. We gossip.
Yeah. We gossip a lot.
He gossips! No, no. You're
missing the point. Okay?
We see a great-looking
guy like Gregory,
and we say he's gay because
we want him to be gay.
Really? Really? Are you sure?
Yes.
Absolutely. Look at what
we do with movie stars.
You know? Hugh Jackman.
He sings, he dances, he's dreamy.
So obviously we would want him on our team.
Mmm!
But he's straight.
Trust me. I know.
I said hello to him once
in a restaurant,
and there was absolutely
no chemistry.
Well, if that isn't proof-
Three weeks later, Sandy
and Gregory got married,
and everyone said the
wedding was beautiful.
Gregory did the flowers.
Which is perfectly normal
for a straight guy.
The Greeks do one thing
right, and it's lamb.
All right, let's go vote.
Why the hell does your wife want to be
a politician anyway? You heard her.
She wanted to put up a stop sign at Bristol
and Greenleaf, but then she ran into-
Wait, wait, wait.
That's near where I live.
Yeah! We're neighbors.
Let's go.
No way I'm votin' for that.
Too much government already.
I didn't fight a war so some politician
can tell me where I have to stop my car.
You don't even drive!
That's 'cause that Barack Obama
took my license away.
I don't think he was involved
in the decision!
I left the house today to get 50 votes for my wife.
I'm not going home with zero.
The least you can do is walk right in
there and punch a hole for the woman ...
who drags your garbage can
up your driveway every Tuesday!
I don't like it.
Goes against everything I believe in.
- Really? A stop sign?
- But I'll do it.
'Cause you're a good kid,
and I had a nice day.
Till you started yelling at me.
So sorry.
Thank you.
Here you go.
You know, my wife
was an alcoholic too.
Okay.
Let's just go vote.
The polls are closed
for the District 43 town council race-
Hi, everyone!
Any news?
Not yet, not yet.
But even if I lose, at least now
I know I have a future in radio.
I couldn't.
People need to see me.
Before we hear the results,
I just want to thank you all for
everything you've done for me.
Mitch and Cam,
for campaigning for me all day
in your little Claire-mobile.
It's the least
we could do.
Literally.
We probably did more for Hugh Jackman's
career than we did for Claire's.
And Manny and Gloria, thank you
for making all those phone calls.
And Dad,
for all your support.
I don't think I convinced
anyone to vote for Claire.
I don't think I even voted.
And my husband.
Who drove around I don't know how many
senior citizens today to the polls.
One.
And my beautiful children,
whose faith has given me the confidence
to believe that I can do this.
I can- Oh!
Somebody else answer it.
It's- I lost. I can feel it.
Mom. Mom.
Answer the phone.
Hello.
This is she.
Mm-hmm.
Thanks so much for calling.
Bye-bye.
I have some bad news.
Because someone's gonna be busy
now that she's a councilwoman?
No, no, no!
No, I wasn't doing that fake thing.
I really lost. I lost.
Ay, no.
- That's all right.
- I'm so sorry.
But you know what?
We are still
just so proud of you.
Yeah.
I don't know about you, but, um,
I could use a glass of wine.
Now you're gonna
hear her drunk voice.
Hmm.
Mom.
Mmm?
- You okay?
- Yes, fine. I'm good. I'm fine.
I'm not fine.
I wanted to win, and-
and I'm so embarrassed.
Everybody out there
worked so hard for me ...
and they believed in me,
and I let 'em down.
Oh! Honey.
Oh, sweetheart.
Well, don't cry.
I'm gonna be fine, sweetie.
Really, I am.
Just knowing you care
so much makes me feel better.
No.
I got four rejection letters
I never told you guys about.
What?
I got rejected from UCSB,
Oregon, Wisconsin-
Oh, no.
Northwestern.
Well, we were overshooting
on that one.
What about, uh-
Came today.
My last chance.
Mm-hmm.
I'm too scared
to open it.
Whatever it says in there, your father
and I are crazy proud of you. Okay?
I did start trying this year.
I know you did.
You did. You have nothing
to be ashamed of.
Neither do you.
Mmm.
It's a little bit different.
No, it's exactly
the same.
Except you tried really hard the
whole time, not just at the end.
You're right.
It is the same.
We have nothing to be ashamed of.
So let's open that together.
Yeah, open it.
What? No.
- What are you doing here?
- No, come on, Haley. We believe in you.
Do it!  You
can always work for me.
You can do it.
Come on, Haley.
All right, open,
open, open, open.
"Dear Ms. Dunphy,
we regret to inform you-"
Oh, honey.
Mm-hmm.
"While we cannot offer you
admission at this time,
you are a promising candidate, and therefore
we would like to place you on our wait list."
Oh, my God,
I got wait-listed!
We will take it!
Haley!
Congratulations!
Our daughter might be
going to college!
Phil! Look!
- A stop sign.
- It's addressed to you.
"Dear Claire,
I won, you lost.
Here is your stupid
stop sign.
Next time you think about bothering
me, please take its advice.
Your councilman,
the Honorable Duane Bailey."
- Blaaah!
- Honey, you did it!
I did it. I made our
neighborhood a little bit safer.
I may even have saved a life.
You idiot! There's a stop sign!
Can't you read?
We need speed bumps.
No.
Mmm. No. No! Honey!
English - US - PSDH