This week the
world lost a great man,
and I lost a mentor.
For nearly 60 years
Professor Ringmaster Al Uzielli ...
helped young hopefuls like me
find their clown persona.
Professor Ringmaster?
It's a very prestigious title
at clown college.
One step below
Piemaster General.
Where's Lewis?
Who knows?
Okay, guys, it's just us.
Lift on three.
# Hey, hey #
# Hey ##
Hey, how come you guys haven't
accepted my friend requests?
I didn't know
you were on Facebook.
Yeah, you said it was only for teenagers
and people looking to have affairs.
Well, I figured
if you can't fight it-
Not having the affair.
That's still bad. No, not that.
But there's nothing wrong with catching
up with a few old friends, right?
Or doin' a little social
networking with my B.F.F.'s.
Mmm.
Yeah.
Social networking
or social not-working?
Oh, you know what we gotta do? We gotta get
a picture of us all together on a boat.
I think that's a thing now. So what do you say?
Accept my friend thingy.
Sorry, Mom, I- I didn't get
a friend thingy from you.
Yeah, you know, they have a lot of blocks
on there to protect kids from weirdos.
Mmm, okay. Good, good.
I'll send it again. Great.
Please do.
Please don't.
We got her request
the first time, but ignored it.
I can't have her on there
snooping around,
seeing what I'm doing
at parties.
Or posting pictures of us
on family vacations ...
wearing old, dorky clothes.
What?
What's wrong
with this?
Dad, check it out.
I made one giant Oreo.
Luke, what are you doing?
- You gotta eat it like it's an ear of corn.
- Genius.
Oh.
Wow. New suit.
New everything.
Kids, gather round.
it's time for a life lesson.
Aren't we
already gathered?
Let me tell you something.
Hard work, determination
and perseverance always win out.
I am living proof that
nice guys can finish first.
Today I have
a chance to get ...
the biggest listing
of my career.
Oh, I have never seen
this man so focused.
I'm like a boxer
before the big fight.
That's why I didn't have sex with
Claire last night. Sorry, honey.
Mmm. No, it's-
it's okay.
But as soon as I get this listing- ding!
Let's just stop.
Stop.
I see you. What? I'm scratching.
Hey, Mom, is it okay if I have
a friend come over tomorrow?
Who? Reuben?
Or the nervous one
that gets the nosebleed?
It's Griffin Cooper.
Griffin Cooper?
Griffin Cooper is by far ...
the coolest kid in Manny's grade.
He's a terrific athlete.
He's confident.
Manny's a great kid, sure,
but he's not exactly cool.
He can't even
open a door cool.
Salutations, Wyatt.
I'm so glad you're joining me
for an afternoon of mirth.
Good evening,
Reuben-san.
May I ask you
to remove your shoes?
Tonight
we are going Japanese.
Ah!
I invented a new language
this morning.
When did you guys
become buddies?
Was it a football game in the yard?
You made a great catch?
No, that didn't happen. But the librarian
told me one day I'll be a great catch.
Well, I'm really not
getting that relationship.
Why can't you just be happy that
Manny's making new friends?
'Cause
it doesn't add up.
Cool kids like Griffin Cooper, they
don't hang out with kids like Manny.
Manny's very cool.
Maybe those kids
are finally catching up to him.
Wait a minute. I get it.
Couple of days last week, I took
Manny to school on my motorcycle.
Griffin must think
I'm pretty boss.
Yes, Jay.
it's all because of you.
Kids are lookin' for role models.
Why do you think Fonzie
was so popular?
He told people that they were rich, but
really took their money with his scheme?
No, that's a-
Yes.
Those people were victims
of a Fonzie scheme.
Mmm.
Whew.
it's showtime.
Hey, Dunphy. You gettin' ready
for your one-woman show?
Mitzi.
Mitzi Roth.
A notorious poacher in the world of
high-end residential real estate.
We call her
the nightmare on Elm Street ...
because she sold a lot
of houses on Elm Street.
What are you doing here, Mitzi? I have
an appointment. This is my listing.
Oh, I didn't think that was
dotted-line yet, jazz hands.
No worries.
I may have an interested buyer.
I'll bring him to you.
Really?
Okay, but could you come back later? I
really need to have 'em to myself right now.
Oh, yeah, okay. I completely understand.
Okay. Thanks.
You're welcome.
Wait. What?
What are you doing?
Watch this.  Hello?
It's Mitzi Roth.
And Phil Dunphy.
I may have a prospective buyer
for your beautiful house.
I was wondering if maybe I could
come in- Hey, Stan. Hey, Patti.
And just have a look
for a little while.
We got a lot to talk about.
Come on in.
Um-
Hey, guys, yeah, I'm wondering if
maybe we shouldn't be alone for this.
I'm in.
Go back to condos,
Dunphy.
Oh, my God, this place
is absolutely gorgeous.
Stunning. Stunning.
You are in such good
hands with Phil.
Hey.
How are you GUYS?
I mean,
fingers crossed though.
You know, so many new companies
go belly-up. Terrible.
Well, good to-
good to see you, Mitzi.
Guys, how are you? Oh, no, no. it's fine.
it's fine. Come take a look.
Oh, thank you.
Mitzi, please.
Thank you.
Please.
What are you doing? Oh, my God!
He shoved me!
What?
- For God's sake! Phil!
- Oh, my God!
I thought you had your anger
problem under control.
I don't have an anger-
I don't- Anger problem-
I don't have an anger problem.
Oh, hey. it's over?
What the hell?
- You're an hour late.
- Good to see you too, Chuckleberry.
Look at that. Your oversized
pants are startin' to fit.
Hello, Lewis.
Hello, Fizbo.
For several years,
I was one half of ...
the renowned clown duo
Fizbo and Lewis.
We were huge.
In children's parties.
Anyway, I disbanded the group
shortly after I met Mitchell.
It's hard to have a relationship
and a clown career.
That's the reason there are
so many single clowns.
It's just
one of the reasons.
Anyway, um, Lewis
hasn't spoken to me since.
He's still bitter,
and I don't blame him.
It's kind of like
I broke up the Beatles.
Of children's parties.
What do you say we hit a bar?
Tip a few back to Al, huh?
I heard you were in jail. Yeah?
I heard you're still doin' that lame
giant-scissors bit, you blue-haired hack.
Who's in? I'll go.
Just give me a minute.
I gotta redo my lips.
All right. Cerveza.
What about you,
Fizzy?
You gonna come, or are you gonna
break up this party too'?
Hey, shotgun, bitches!
I should, you know, probably go.
You know, for- for Al.
Oh, yeah. No, of course. But listen,
don't let him get to you, all right?
No, it's fine. it's all
seltzer under the bridge.
Just one drink
and then I'll be home.
Okay. Just drive me home first?
No, you- you take the car.
I, uh-
I'll go with the guys.
In that tiny car? How are
you all possibly gonna-
Forget I asked.
It's 5:00 in the morning.
Daddy's juggling.
Lily, honey, what-
what are you doing up?
Are you just getting home? Yeah,
things got a little out of hand.
Somebody had a ?ower
that squirted tequila.
What do you mean, "somebody"?
I want full credit.
What up, red? Really?
Teach me to juggle! it's very simple.
The key is to be aware of where
everything is at all times.
And don't forget the
importance of balance- Whoa!
- Okay, okay. Come on.
- I think I cracked my eggs.
We're out of eggs?
Are you yolking?
I haven't eaten in five days!
Five days?
Are you cereal?
Whoa!
Lily,
don't ever do that.
Okay. You two are deliberately
not confirming me.
Everybody else has
accepted my friend requests.
Your father.
Uncle Mitchell.
Adele.
That's right.
Adele has agreed to be my friend,
and my own daughters haven't.
Yeah, you may just be
a fan of Adele and not-
What is so private
that I can't possibly see it?
Nothing.
Nothing. So you just ...
don't want to be my friend.
That's great. I can see
my next status update.
"My daughters
are monsters."
You're
not gonna believe this.
Mitzi got the listing.
Oh, no, honey.
That's awful!
She cheated, she lied,
and she won.
Kids, gather round.
Again, we are gathered.
You want to get ahead?
Don't play by the rules.
Turns out nice guys finish last
in this cold, dog-eat-dog world.
It's not fair. Why don't you play dirty too?
You could take her down.
Honey, 'cause your dad
is a better man than that.
He has values and morals and- Shh.
You. Keep talking.
Well, just off
the top of my head,
you could take my spy pen and
record her admitting what she did.
And then you could play it for those people
so they'd realize what a jerk she is.
Your dad is never
gonna do that.
You're a regular chatterbox today.
Get me that pen.
I got it.  Remember,
pal, keep it simple.
Hey, Manny.
Griffin, the legendary
creature of Greek mythology ...
with the head of a lion
and wings of an eagle.
What'd you say, Jay?
Never mind.
Jay Pritchett.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to
meet you too.
You know, I, uh-
I saw a little of that basketball
game of yours last week.
You were lightin' it up. Thanks.
I was lighting it up
too, Jay.
Who's hot? We're hot!
Mustangs are hot!
Brrrr! Whoo!
Brrrr! Hey!
Hola, Griffin.
How are you?
Uh- Oh!
Thirteen.
I'm fine.
So what do you boys
have planned for today?
Well, it's kind of a surprise for Griffin,
but let's just say it involves decoupage.
Oh, geez.
Come on. Let's go.
Good-bye.
Oh, no.
What?
You were right.
This boy is not here
to see Manny.
I told you. You see the
way he looks at me?
No, Fonzie,
the way he looks at me.
He couldn't talk.
He kept staring.
He was just like my teachers
back in school.
Gloria, you're very pretty,
but the kid idolizes me.
Really?
Griffin! Manny!
Do you want to go with Jay
to ride his motorcycle,
or you want to go with me to the
supermarket and buy a couple of onions?
Motorcycle rides!
Onions sound good.
Huh.
Guess he has
a thing for you too.
Hey.
We're back.
Hey, I- I just finished
cleaning the kitchen,
so if anyone has to do a spit
take, please do it over the sink.
We felt really bad about that,
so we got you a present.
Wh-What's the deal with this? I open it
up, and snakes fly out, or a fire, or-
No. We just know that you like to read.
So open it. Yeah.
- Ah! Got him!
- No. No.
That's exactly what I expected.
Remember when I told you?
Okay, look, it's almost go time. So we
should have a shot and go white up.
Excuse me.
White up?
Oh, yeah, Lewis got a call to do
a birthday party this afternoon,
so we're gonna put
the old act back together.
Yeah, Fizbo and Lewis, together again.
And they said it would never happen.
Said. Hoped. Could I talk
to you for a second?
Uh-oh.
Trouble in queeradise.
Okay, look, gonna go out
to the car for smokes.
Please tell me "smokes"
is not another clown.
'Cause I don't think I could handle another
one of him. Lewis is not that bad.
- What do you see in that guy, Cam?
- I don't know.
Maybe the fact that he doesn't roll his eyes
every time I talk about the art of clowning.
Like that.
He may have had his faults,
but we were great together.
We had an unspoken language. We
finished each other's balloon animals.
But you would never know, because you have
never been to one of our performances.
Birthday parties.
You hate my clown side.
No.
No, no.
I don't hate it.
Just admit it.
I basically already know you do.
Okay, okay.
Cards on the table.
- It's not my favorite thing that you-
- Oh, how dare you!
I am a clown.
it's who I am.
If you squeeze me,
do I not honk?
Eye roll. Oh, like
I had a choice.
Knock-knock.
What are you
doing here?
Hey, um, I-
I brought you some soup.
You know, I thought about it,
and maybe I did push you.
So, how's the ankle?
Oh, come on, Dunphy.
You know I flopped.
Haven't you ever seen
an NBA game?
Oh, I'm sorry.
In your case, WNBA.
So that was all a ruse?
The oldest trick in the book. You
need to step up your game, son.
You know what?
I almost feel sorry for you.
Come here.
Give me a big hug.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
No hard feelings, huh?
None at all.
Good. Because I just recorded
your entire confession.
Right here on my-
Spy Den?
Second-oldest trick
in the book.
Um-  Oh, God.
A real man would have
just poisoned the soup.
Are we done here?
Ah, thank you.
Hey, Mom!
Guess what!
Griffin invited us all over to his house
for a pool party and barbecue tonight.
- Pool party, huh?
- Yeah, and he said bring your swimsuits.
He was pretty adamant
about it.
It's 50 degrees outside.
Sounds fun. Great.
I'll call him.
You know, you're basically agreeing
to a date with a 13-year-old boy.
Jay, we use this to get us
tables at restaurants.
Why can't we use this
to get Manny a friend?
Because he's not really
getting a friend. Oh.
But when you thought that he was trying
to ride your motorcycle, it was okay.
Maybe now I don't like
what he's trying to ride.
Manny likes Griffin.
Maybe someday, if they spend enough
time together, Griffin will like Manny.
What?
Griffin doesn't like me?
No, no, no, papi,
he loves you.
But you just said someday Griffin will like me.
That means he doesn't like me now.
You know what, kid?
We think that Griffin ...
might be
hanging out with you ...
because he's got a little
crush on your mother and me.
On you? Wow. I can't believe it.
Listen, it's fine. You're gonna be fine.
I'm sorry.
Are you kidding? it's fantastic!
How is it fantastic?
I'm only hanging out with him because
I have the hots for his sister Chloe.
You've met Griffin.
The kid's a doorknob.
So you're
just using him?
Yeah, and I felt
really guilty about it until now.
Now it's a win-win.
Not for me.
Just suck it up, Mom.
I've done a lot for you over the years.
Jay, you too.
This girl could be the one. Then
I'm out of your hair forever.
Pool party, Mom.
Dress accordingly.
Can you help me reach that
box of cereal?
Hey.
You're Mitzi Roth. I
recognized you from your ads.
Smokin', right?
I'm Luke Dunphy.
My dad's Phil Dunphy.
I'm sorry.
Why do you hate him
so much?
It's just business, kid.
It's not personal.
Well, it's personal to us.
I've never seen my dad
so worried before.
I have this spy pen, and I
heard him talking to my mom,
and he's scared about paying for
my sister's college next year.
And I guess he's nervous
about some kind of party,
because he said there's
a big balloon payment.
Anyways, he's, like,
the best dad ever,
so maybe you could be
a little nicer to him.
There you are,
buddy.
Check it out. They're giving
away free jelly beans.
Hi, Mitzi.
Dunphy.
You have
a very nice kid there.
He's mine.
Hey. So I was thinking-
After Little Fizbo,
we could do the ladder bit.
Ah, crap,
I forgot the ladder.
You know what? I'll
remember it next weekend.
What's next weekend?
We got a town fair
in Thousand Oaks ...
and a birthday party
in Pasadena.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
I- I can't do that.
What do you mean? I'm the one with
outstanding warrants in Pasadena.
No, we're taking Lily to
the aquarium next weekend.
You know, Lewis, this was
just a one-time thing, right?
Well, what happened to we're
puttin' the act back together?
Well, that was
just for today.
Oh.
Oh, sure.
I'm sorry if you thought- No, no, no.
I get it.
You're a family man now.
Hey.
Let's go out there and make this the best
show Fizbo and Lewis have ever done.
You got it, partner.
Ladies and germs,
boys and girls,
say hello to my good friend,
Little Fizbo!
Hello, big people.
Hi!
Let's get this party started!
Wow, all this dancing
sure has made me hungry.
Wish I had something to eat.
Oh, forgot I had
that fish over there.
Don't know why he's so mad at me.
He was fine just a minute ago.
Oh! Okay. Somebody's
a little punchy today.
Hey, what's the frying pan
doing here?
When did we add a frying pan to the act?
Nope, don't need the frying pan.
Why are you doing that?
Stop doing that.
- Screw you, you traitor.
- Ow! That hurts! Seriously. Stop it.
You know what hurts?
Abandonment.
Listen to 'em laughing.
We could've been something.
We could've been-
I can't do this bit by myself!
Somebody- Somebody-
This isn't pretend!
Someone grab an adult, please!
Mitzi. Your kid
forgot his cereal.
There's a surprise
in every box.
it's diabetes.
You drove all the way
over here for this?
Okay, look, here's the deal. You can
have that listing if you want it.
What? Yeah. The couple
are a real pain.
I'm too old for
that kind of headache.
Just keep your mouth shut about it.
Thank you so much.
I just said zip it!
Oh. You did-
Unbelievable.
I'm so sorry. But thank you.
Bye.
Kids, gather round!
We are right here!
Oh.
Let me tell you
something.
People are
fundamentally good.
The key is, you find that
goodness deep within them,
twist it and turn it
to your advantage.
Hello.
Pshh!
And there she is.
What are you
gonna hit?
College, balloon payment,
greatest dad ever.
- Nice. You want me to squirt some tears in your eyes?
- Dad, please.
I was fake crying
before I could walk.
How do you think I got out
of eating all those salads?
Can you help me reach that
box of cereal?
Oh, hey, you're
Mitzi Roth, right?
I recognized you
from your ads.
Smokin', huh?
I can't believe you got that
listing back, honey! Sweetheart!
Ohh.
Honey.
Mm-hmm?
Ding.
Are you sure you want
to ding a chatterbox?
Hmm.
Wh- Uh-
Honey.
Quick. What's the trick
to those fake tears?
The Three Stooges
are all dead.
Yeah, that's good.
Well, it looks like
somebody likes Coldplay.
Hmm. Right. You saw.
Uh-huh.
Did you see the pictures
I posted from Thanksgiving?
Totes adorbs. I'm
going to kill myself.
You gotta check out my wall.
Right there.
"Spring Break, 1990,
New Orleans."
Is that you?
What?
Some guy from your college
tagged you in a picture.
What is tagging? What is tagging?
Why are you drinking
out of a funnel?
And why is his hand on your-
Untag it! Un- Untag it!
Oh, my goodness!
Girls, I'm serious!
Untag it! Tear down the wall!
English - US - PSDH