Hey, sir.
Duane Bailey, running
for town council reelection.
Oh, don't look. There's
that jerk Duane Bailey.
Oh, yuck.
I should say something
to him, shouldn't I?
I gotta be honest. I was
just working off your tone.
Who's Duane Bailey,
and why do we hate him?
Honey, he's that councilman who
shot down my stop sign. Big phony.
Yeah. Hey.
Duane Bailey,
seeking reelection,
town council.
Hoping I can count on your vote.
Well, you just got it.
Phil.
You don't remember
meeting me, do you?
Claire Dunphy. Last month's
town council meeting?
Oh, yes, I do.
Yes, I remember you.
"I want a stop sign."
Just having fun.
Here. Have a pen.
"Duane Bailey. Councilman.
Citizen. Puggle breeder."
I love them because they're
a different mix of breeds.
Just like America.
- I like what he's saying, Claire.
- He isn't saying anything.
He is. We need a stop
sign at our intersection.
Everyone says that,
but pretty soon, we're stopping
at every single corner.
Why don't you go ask Canada
how that's working out?
Hi. Duane Bailey. Hi.
Nailed it.
"Actor-writer-director
who packs a punch."
Oh, Sylvester Stallone. I said it first.
Sylvester Stallone.
Oh, my God. This guy
brought his kids, Mitchell.
My God. To this movie? isn't it
supposed to be super violent?
I'm sorry.
I don't mean to overstep,
but I don't know that this movie
is really appropriate for children.
I'm terrified to see it. That's
why we're here during the day.
It's okay. We're good.
Okay. I tried.
Yeah.
All you can do.
You know,
I've read this book,
and I know what's gonna happen,
and it's very disturbing.
I really think you might be inviting
some pretty serious nightmares here.
Hey, buddy,
they're my kids. I got it.
Yeah, but I don't think you do. Cam. Cam.
He says he's got it, all right?
You've said your piece.
Just watch the movie.
Oh, uh, Gwyneth Paltrow.
I really must insist you
not traumatize your kids...
by exposing them to gratuitous
violence- Cam. Stop it.
And graphic depictions of-
Shh, shh.
Daddy, I'm scared.
- Yeah, well, you're gonna be.
- I'm gonna tell you one more time.
No, I'm gonna tell you
one more time. Okay.
It was The Muppet Movie.
We were
in the wrong theater.
Enjoy the show. I was always
a fan of the Muppets,
especially the two guys in the
theater who wouldn't shut up.
Just leave!
# Hey, hey #
# Hey ##
Hello?  I'm running late.
This knucklehead's kept me
waiting for over an hour.
I never had to wait like this
when his dad was running things.
Yeah.
And soda was a nickel.
Just tell him
that your family is coming over.
This guy fired his own father.
He's not gonna care about my family.
Okay, then just leave.
You don't need his money.
Once a week, I have eight family members
coming to my house for free food.
I'm not going anywhere.
Okay.
I see you when I see you.
Are you okay? What is wrong?
I wanna be homeschooled.
Really, Manny?
Do you want me
to learn you English?
What is going on?
I have a big report due in. The teachers
don't seem to care about the substance.
All they care about is the flash.
Manny, sometimes you can be
a little bit old-fashioned.
Remember the first time you saw the
kids with the backpacks with wheels...
and you thought
they were too flashy?
You're going to school,
not boarding a flight to Denver.
It's getting absurd. Reuben freestyle-rapped
his report on Irish immigrants.
That doesn't even make sense.
Maybe you do a Riverdance. Maybe.
What is your report on?
The mafia.
Perfect.
We do a papier-méché tommy gun.
No, we shouldn't have
to jazz it up.
Then we go upstairs and we get your old
rocking horse and we chop the head off.
No, that's a terrible idea.
I love Brownie.
Do you want to send
a message or not?
Jay never wants me
to help him with his business.
And now suddenly, Manny doesn't
want to listen to me either.
It's very frustrating.
I have all the answers.
Hey, here he is!
Hey, bring it in, Jay.
How you doing, Joshie?
It's Josh now. Have a seat.
Ah. All right.
So, I flipped through your
proposal, and here's the thing.
We're about to build our largest
luxury condo complex yet,
and I have
an important question for you.
What is it
you wanna build?
Closets.
See, I was kinda hoping
you'd say dreams.
Thought that was implied.
Jay, I'm looking for closets
nobody's ever seen before.
You know, a big "wow!"
You know what I'm saying?
You want a nice closet with sharp design,
quality materials and expert craftsmanship.
Uh, I mean, I want it
to be like- Barn!
You know, people are gonna walk in there
and go, "Whoa! What do I hang first?"
I wanted to hang myself.
Let's talk more specific.
What exactly do you like,
and what don't you like?
All right, fair enough.
Uh, I don't like this.
This makes me sad.
I do like
getting my mind blown.
I love your enthusiasm.
Uh, before I go off in the wrong
direction, how about an example?
All right, check this out. So three
weeks ago, I'm down in South Beach.
I walk into this thumpin' club.
Bartender says, "What do you
wanna drink?" I say, "Wow me."
He mixes this thing together. I take
one sip, and I'm like, "Hello, nurse!"
And she's like, "You've
been unconscious for two days."
That's what I want in a closet.
I don't think
I need to hear any more.
What you doing there,
homework?
- What do you want?
- I need to borrow some money.
It's really important.
How much?
$900.
What?
Come on.
If you were in trouble,
I would do anything for you.
We're not just sisters.
We're best friends.
Look, I would if I could,
but I don't have any money.
And since we're talking,
I- I've never told anyone
this before, and it-
Wipe that smug smile
off his stupid face.
His face is stupid.
Oh, I can't believe ridiculous
people like him end up in office.
Well, why don't you run?
You're smart.
You care about the community.
And you're easy on the eyes
when you put a little effort into it.
- Are you serious?
- Yeah.
Maybe change out of the sweaty gym
clothes every once in a while-
But you were talking about
running for office. Go on.
I'd be lying if I said
I'd never thought about it.
I know it's a ridiculous
little local thing,
but it might be fun to
get out there and contribute.
Plus I think I'd be good at it.
You'd be great.
Mmm.
How would this work? Who would be
here for the kids after school?
Who would take them
to practice and recitals...
and keep them from
burning the house down?
It must be so hard
being a single mom.
Oh-
Claire, I will.
If you wanna fly, I'm not gonna
hold your feet to the ground.
Hmm. I wanna be the one to
push you off the cliff.
I think I'm gonna do it.
Great.
Go fly.
Phil!
No.
I'll admit it.
I'm turned on by powerful women.
Michelle Obama, Oprah, Condoleezza
Rice, Serena Williams-
Wait a minute.
Do you want a fry?
No, I can't eat.
We should've stayed
to see the Muppets.
I can't even look at ketchup
without seeing blood.
Oh, runaway curly fry.
You know, these are good luck.
Oh!
Oh, my God. What was that?
We just got rear-ended.
Well, pull off to the side street.
Pull off to the side street.
Oh! Are you okay? Oh, I think I cut
the roof of my mouth on the straw.
Oh, my God. Mmm!
So yes.
Oh, boy.
I'm so sorry.
This is all my fault.
You guys okay?
Well- Well, I-l sustained
a minor mouth injury.
We're fine, thank you. Look, I feel terrible.
Don't worry. I'm gonna
take care of everything.
Let me just get
my insurance info.
Thank you.
Well, he seems nice.
Yeah.
If this were a romantic comedy,
this would be our meet-cute.
We'd spend the rest of the afternoon
drinking wine, eating food, flying a kite,
you know,
doing montage-y stuff.
Am I in this movie of yours? Yeah,
you're the gay best friend.
Oh, my God!
Oh, my God! We got a runner!
Um, it's D-1- I can't read it.
- Let's go! Let's go!
- Go where?
- We have to chase him down!
- You're not supposed to.
Help! Stop that car!
He's getting away! Help!
You almost got him, Cam.
You almost got him.
He's getting away!
Hey. What you doing, playing?
Yeah.
Do you have any money saved up?
I'm comfortable.
I've saved $1,217.
It wasn't even that hard.
Don't forget your lunch.
Thanks, Mom.
Don't forget
your lunch money, buddy.
Thanks, Dad.
You bet.
Please.
it's really important.
Look, I'd love to help you out,
but I'm not very liquid right now.
It's in a block of ice.
I got the idea when I heard about
rich guyswith frozen assets.
"Ass-ets."
I am running
for town council,
and I understand
that I can pick up a form here.
Fourth floor.
Elevator down the hall.
Beyoncé, when'd you start working here?
Oh, Duane. He's always
saying stuff like that.
Duane Bailey.
Running for reelection.
You're joking.
I just saw you in the
parking lot two hours ago.
Oh!
Hey, it's you. Oh, it's you.
What are you doing here?
I am entering the race for town
council, and I am running against you.
Oh. Well,
don't you have pluck.
No, I plan on winning, so-
Yeah, I bet you do.
Marsha! Rockin' the bangs.
Love it
Do you know why, of all the dogs
in the world, I breed puggles?
Why do I feel like this is a rhetorical
question, and you're about to lau-
it's because
they're lovable, yes,
but they're also tenacious hunters who
won't quit until the kill is complete.
Really? 'Cause I feel
like they just yip a lot.
Look, lady,
you're going down.
I've won six straight elections. I don't
plan on losing to some bored housewife.
So don't quit
your lack of a day job.
Excuse me!
Excuse me! I-
Excuse me.
Hello?
Anne?
Haley did that?
Oh, God. Okay, um-
I'll call you right back.
For your information, sir,
I am no bored housewife.
L-I would kill for bored.
Why isn't this lighting up?
Oh, it's because
it's staff only. The, uh-
Here. Allow me to...
not get that for you.
Good luck!
Dad, I cut my arm.
Oh, wow.
You sure did, buddy.
Ow.
I'll get you fixed up.
Where's Mom?
She belongs
to the people now.
My allergies
are acting up again.
Well, it is your lucky day,
because, missy, Dr. Dad
has everything you need.
Behold the healing powers
of grape flavoring.
- Where's Mom?
- Some people took her.
Drink this.
Listen, guys.
Your mom is taking on more
responsibilities outside of the house.
But don't you worry.
Good old-
Oh, my goodness!
Ow!
I'm so sorry.
You punched me.
Dad, you gave me
the drowsy kind.
There's a drowsy kind?
- I have to study for a test!
- Oh, it really hurts!
Well, I'll get you some ice.
No, no, no, no!
I'll get it.
Oh, you made it.
How was it?
Eh.
Why? What's wrong, babe?
I don't wanna talk about it.
Do it anyways.
This stupid kid's been in the
business about 10 minutes.
He barely looks at my proposal,
and he says he wants more "wow."
What does he mean
by more "wow"?
It's the Bieberization
of America.
What do beavers have
to do with anything?
The beavers, they build the dams all
over the country so there's no floods.
It's the beaverization
of the Americas.
I'm finding there's less and
less we can talk about.
So why didn't you tell him that you've
been in the business for such a long time-
Gloria, it's not gonna make any difference.
He wants to make a change.
And I got a factory full of
people depending on this.
Yeah, but
maybe if you tell him that-
Gloria, please. I've had a tough day.
Can we please not talk about it?
But I want to help. Trust me.
I wish you had the answers.
I do!
Hey, guys.
Hey, Grandpa.
Hey, Grandpa. Hey, Jay.
What's with her? Just tired.
Growth spurt.
Hey, hey.
Hi, guys.
- Hi, baby girl.
- Hola, Lily.
How are you?
Dads are fighting.
No. Uh, we're not fighting.
No, not at all, honey. No. Uh,
go play, sweetheart. Okay?
Let's go play with some blocks. Let's
go stack some blocks. All right.
Okay. The reason we're fighting is
'cause this one thinks he's Dirty Harry.
Having a tough time picturing
Clint Eastwood in that shirt.
Okay, let me ask you something.
Today, at a stoplight,
a guy ran into our car
and then just took off.
I wanted to chase after him.
Mitchell-
Kept a level head
and called the police.
Police. Aren't they too busy
winning the war on drugs?
Okay, so which one of us
did the right thing?
Hit-and-run. Gotta chase 'em down.
I chase the people
all the time.
No, no. That-That's
irresponsible and dangerous.
What if he had been armed? He wasn't armed.
He had a Hillary bumper sticker.
This isn't
an isolated incident.
This morning, he flipped out at somebody
at The Muppet' Movie.
You saw The Muppet' Movie
without me?
- Oh, no.
- No, honey, just the first two numbers.
No. Lily-  Hi, hi, hi.
Phil, where are you, honey?
I need to talk to you.
Do you know
what our daughter did?
Nothing. She's fine.
She's reading.
No, not her. Haley. Haley!
Come over here. I wanna talk to you.
There she is.
Not a scratch on her.
You have something you
wanna say to us? Uh-
Mmm, let me
help you out here.
Fake I.D.'s?
What?
Mm-hmm. Haley tried to get her and
her friends some fake I.D.'s.
I wasn't going to use them
for drinking.
We just wanted to get
into this club to see a band.
She took a bunch of money from
them, and then she lost it.
How much?
$900.
Oh, my God! Oh!
You're kidding me!
It's not my fault! I gave money to this guy.
He's the one who ripped us off.
What happened
to your face?
Oh. I ran into a door.
Yeah.
- What happened to your face?
- Dad hit me.
It was an accident.
Phil!
I was trying to open up a Band-Aid.
- What's wrong with her?
- Growth spurt.
- I drugged her.
Phil- I accidentally gave her
the nighttime allergy medicine.
Mmm. All right,
one thing at a time.
Haley, how are you going
to repay your friends?
I don't know.  I know.
You go there
with a couple of guys-
She's gotta get the money back.
Who is this kid?
A guy at school's cousin's friend.
He lives in Gardena.
Well, if you know where he
lives, just call the police.
No cops. We can't afford
a scandal right now.
Claire's running
for town council.
That was before, when I thought you
could take care of the children.
I take my eye off
the ball for one minute,
and I've got one in a coma, one with a
black eye and one running a crime ring.
Well, to be fair,
Haley started her crime ring...
when your eye
was still on the ball.
It's not a crime ring.
I just gotta get
my hands on that $900.
I know how the mafia
would handle this.
The kid is right.
I'm sick of these smart-ass punks
who keep changing the rules...
and think they can get away
with anything they want.
I'm gonna pay this guy a visit.
Haley, text me his address.
I'm going with you.
Me too.
Oh, no. No. Nobody's going anywhere, okay?
We're not vigilantes.
Shotgun!
No! No weapons!
In my country,
it is tradition.
When the men are out
seeking vengeance,
the women stay home
and they drink.
Sometimes I think
you just make this stuff up.
Do you want a drink or not?
Oh, yeah.
So, what happened?
You were running for office,
and now you're not?
Mmm. I don't really
wanna talk about that.
Ay, no. I am sick and tired
of no one needing my help.
You are going to tell me
what is wrong,
and I'm gonna give you the right
answer, because I have all of them.
So, why are you not
running for office?
Because my family needs me too much.
You saw what just happened.
Why are you not running for office?
Uh, that doesn't work with me.
Why are you
not running for office?
Because I don't want to lose!
I- I haven't done anything
outside of my house in 18 years.
I don't want the first thing I
do to be a complete failure.
Okay.
I'm gonna tell you a story about a little
girl who entered a beauty pageant-
even though ...
She was very, very scared
that she was going to lose.
Let me guess.
You won.
Of course I won. But I was talking
about my cousin Maria Conchita.
She had a nose like a toucan. She
stuff her body in this bikini.
And at the end,
she finish dead last.
How is that a good story?
She faced her fears,
and it didn't kill her.
What killed her
two weeks later was a bus.
Are you serious?
Because she couldn't see anything
coming with that big nose.
This guy has won
six elections.
I am way out of my league.
Look, I don't know
anything about this guy.
But I know
that you're a tough lady,
and I come from a family
of tough ladies.
And I have to say, sometimes
you scare me a little bit.
And I know that you're
strong enough to win...
and definitely strong enough
to be okay if you lose.
I scare you?
Are you kidding me?
"I want
Thanksgiving at my house!"
Why does everybody
think I talk like that?
This is it.
Wait, wait, wait, wait. No, no, come on.
Do we have a plan?
It doesn't seem like we have a plan.
Yeah, I got a plan.
Either he gives us the money, or
he gets a private performance...
from England Dan
and John Ford Coley.
That's not a good plan.
That's not even a good band.
If all you're gonna do is
criticize, just wait by the car.
Okay, fine.
I'll see you in jail.
It's gonna be a big
adjustment for two of you.
Yeah?
You Peter?
What do you want?
You know Haley Dunphy?
You owe her $900. We're
here to collect. You dig?
I tried to call that girl 10 times,
but her voice mail was always full.
That does sound
like Haley.
So how are you
gonna make this right?
You guys want the money, right?
That's fine.
I don't need any hassle.
Hold on.
I'll just-
I'll grab it.
That was easy.
He's lucky
he didn't put up a fight.
I would've treated him to a reunion
of Crosby, Stills, Nash and Young.
- Oh, my God! We got a runner!
- Stop!
- Get him! Get him!
Stop!
No!No!No!
No!
Got him!
- Oh, my God! You did!
- Don't be so surprised!
Help! He's slipping out
of his skinny jeans!
Okay!
These are cute.
I totally have these.
Hmm?
Ah-ha-ha.
Oh! There you go.
Oh, you got it back!
Thank you!
Hey, don't thank me.
Thank your Uncle Mitchell.
He's the one who tackled the guy.
I got grass stains.
Well, I will
tell you one thing.
I have learned my lesson.
Disappointing my family and
friends is punishment enough.
Nice try. You're
grounded for two weeks.
Okay, we have big news.
Claire has decided
to run for mayor after all.
Thank you.
it's town council.
It doesn't matter.
You're not going to win anyways.
But she's going to be okay.
You see?
I help the people. Why don't
you two let me help you?
Well, I can't
speak for Jay,
but I guess I'm just too
proud to ask for help.
Are you serious?
She cuts your steak.
- What about you?
- I don't wanna bother you with my business.
- What else do I do every day?
- I don't know.
I'm guessing the gym
and... one other thing.
Dad, you should listen to her.
She might really help you.
Huh.
She could be an asset.
"Ass-et."
Heard it.
Hmm.
And look at the shelves
over here.
They're for the shoes.
Those are my favorite ones.
So what did you think?
Wow.
Same exact closet.
We never needed fake I.D.'s
on a farm.
We figured if a 16-year-old could drive
a tractor, he could drink a beer.
Not at the same time, of course.
it's Missouri, not Texas.
I used a fake I.D.
to get into an R-rated movie.
The Fabulous Baker Boys.
I found the title
to be misleading.
Lot of Michelle Pfeiffer.
That's all I'm saying.
I remember
when I got my fake I.D.
- Me too. Crazy times.
- Hell, yeah.
I tried to enlist in the army,
but they saw right through me.
So me and a bunch of guys
drove across state lines.
We got a bunch of booze.
We loaded up on fireworks.
And I woke up in the morning,
I kid you not, in a Mexican strip joint.
I .
Oh, I used mine to rent
some bowling shoes and kept 'em.
Suckers probably spent months
trying to track down Dr. Richard Hertz.
Think about it.
English - US - PSDH